{
	"description": "Japanese family names",
	"deck": [
	{ "question": "千葉", "answers": [ "ちば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "福岡", "answers": [ "ふくおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "鈴木", "answers": [ "すずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "佐藤", "answers": [ "さとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田中", "answers": [ "たなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山口", "answers": [ "やまぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%" },
	{ "question": "高橋", "answers": [ "たかはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小林", "answers": [ "こばやし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "長野", "answers": [ "ながの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "徳川", "answers": [ "とくがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山本", "answers": [ "やまもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "渡辺", "answers": [ "わたなべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中村", "answers": [ "なかむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "石川", "answers": [ "いしかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%" },
	{ "question": "加藤", "answers": [ "かとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "福島", "answers": [ "ふくしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "伊藤", "answers": [ "いとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松本", "answers": [ "まつもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "井上", "answers": [ "いのうえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉田", "answers": [ "よしだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "山田", "answers": [ "やまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "松平", "answers": [ "まつだいら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "森", "answers": [ "もり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "藤原", "answers": [ "ふじわら", "ふじはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "長崎", "answers": [ "ながさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "宮城", "answers": [ "みやぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "宮崎", "answers": [ "みやざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%" },
	{ "question": "池田", "answers": [ "いけだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "富山", "answers": [ "とみやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "秋田", "answers": [ "あきた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "源", "answers": [ "みなもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "前田", "answers": [ "まえだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "奈良", "answers": [ "なら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "福井", "answers": [ "ふくい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "木村", "answers": [ "きむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山形", "answers": [ "やまがた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "神戸", "answers": [ "かんべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "林", "answers": [ "はやし", "りん", "リン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "佐々木", "answers": [ "ささき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清水", "answers": [ "しみず", "しみずの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "織田", "answers": [ "おだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "香川", "answers": [ "かがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "高知", "answers": [ "たかち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "山梨", "answers": [ "やまなし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "足利", "answers": [ "あしかが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "石井", "answers": [ "いしい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "岡田", "answers": [ "おかだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "渋谷", "answers": [ "しぶや", "しぶたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "村上", "answers": [ "むらかみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "三浦", "answers": [ "みうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "橋本", "answers": [ "はしもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "中島", "answers": [ "なかじま", "なかしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "坂本", "answers": [ "さかもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "仙台", "answers": [ "せんだい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "誠", "answers": [ "まこと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "長谷川", "answers": [ "はせがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "近藤", "answers": [ "こんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "後藤", "answers": [ "ごとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "藤田", "answers": [ "ふじた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "石田", "answers": [ "いしだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "原", "answers": [ "はら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "李", "answers": [ "り", "イ", "リー", "リ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%, 27%, 6%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "阿部", "answers": [ "あべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "斎藤", "answers": [ "さいとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山崎", "answers": [ "やまざき", "やまさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "酒井", "answers": [ "さかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中野", "answers": [ "なかの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%" },
	{ "question": "松田", "answers": [ "まつだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "田村", "answers": [ "たむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "小野", "answers": [ "おの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "西村", "answers": [ "にしむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中山", "answers": [ "なかやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "武田", "answers": [ "たけだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "山下", "answers": [ "やました" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "川崎", "answers": [ "かわさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 27%" },
	{ "question": "剛", "answers": [ "ごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "細川", "answers": [ "ほそかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大塚", "answers": [ "おおつか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "港", "answers": [ "みなと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "隆", "answers": [ "りゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "伊達", "answers": [ "だて" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "太田", "answers": [ "おおた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "平", "answers": [ "たいら", "ひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "遠藤", "answers": [ "えんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "福田", "answers": [ "ふくだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "小川", "answers": [ "おがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "原田", "answers": [ "はらだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "島田", "answers": [ "しまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "上田", "answers": [ "うえだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "岡本", "answers": [ "おかもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "内田", "answers": [ "うちだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "上杉", "answers": [ "うえすぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "柴田", "answers": [ "しばた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "伊東", "answers": [ "いとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "青木", "answers": [ "あおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "横山", "answers": [ "よこやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "野村", "answers": [ "のむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "水野", "answers": [ "みずの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "金", "answers": [ "キム", "きん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "松山", "answers": [ "まつやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%" },
	{ "question": "松井", "answers": [ "まつい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝", "answers": [ "かつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%" },
	{ "question": "和田", "answers": [ "わだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "安藤", "answers": [ "あんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "市川", "answers": [ "いちかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%" },
	{ "question": "小山", "answers": [ "こやま", "おやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "永井", "answers": [ "ながい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "石原", "answers": [ "いしはら", "いしわら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "吉川", "answers": [ "よしかわ", "きっかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 33%" },
	{ "question": "武", "answers": [ "たけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%" },
	{ "question": "中川", "answers": [ "なかがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "高田", "answers": [ "たかだ", "たかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "藤井", "answers": [ "ふじい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宮本", "answers": [ "みやもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "島津", "answers": [ "しまづ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竹内", "answers": [ "たけうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "金子", "answers": [ "かねこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "南", "answers": [ "みなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "関", "answers": [ "せき", "かん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "毛利", "answers": [ "もうり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浅野", "answers": [ "あさの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "高松", "answers": [ "たかまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "大島", "answers": [ "おおしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "堺", "answers": [ "さかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "菊池", "answers": [ "きくち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "中田", "answers": [ "なかた", "なかだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "大久保", "answers": [ "おおくぼ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "斉藤", "answers": [ "さいとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "本多", "answers": [ "ほんだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "内藤", "answers": [ "ないとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "青山", "answers": [ "あおやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "張", "answers": [ "ちょう", "チャン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "高木", "answers": [ "たかぎ", "たかき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "大野", "answers": [ "おおの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%" },
	{ "question": "福山", "answers": [ "ふくやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%" },
	{ "question": "高山", "answers": [ "たかやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%" },
	{ "question": "小泉", "answers": [ "こいずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "黒田", "answers": [ "くろだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "浜田", "answers": [ "はまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%" },
	{ "question": "上野", "answers": [ "うえの", "うわの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "今井", "answers": [ "いまい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "小島", "answers": [ "こじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "松尾", "answers": [ "まつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "豊田", "answers": [ "とよだ", "とよた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "金沢", "answers": [ "かなざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "星野", "answers": [ "ほしの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桂", "answers": [ "かつら", "ケイ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "三木", "answers": [ "みき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%" },
	{ "question": "佐野", "answers": [ "さの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "東", "answers": [ "あずま", "ひがし", "とう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 18%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "藤本", "answers": [ "ふじもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小松", "answers": [ "こまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%" },
	{ "question": "宇都宮", "answers": [ "うつのみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%" },
	{ "question": "森田", "answers": [ "もりた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "品川", "answers": [ "しながわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "劉", "answers": [ "りゅう", "ユ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "西田", "answers": [ "にしだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山内", "answers": [ "やまうち", "やまのうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "岡崎", "answers": [ "おかざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%" },
	{ "question": "平野", "answers": [ "ひらの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "戸田", "answers": [ "とだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "堀", "answers": [ "ほり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桜井", "answers": [ "さくらい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "野田", "answers": [ "のだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%" },
	{ "question": "孫", "answers": [ "そん", "スン", "ソン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 3%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "安田", "answers": [ "やすだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "工藤", "answers": [ "くどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秋元", "answers": [ "あきもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "木下", "answers": [ "きのした" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "菅原", "answers": [ "すがわら", "すがはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "尾崎", "answers": [ "おざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "松岡", "answers": [ "まつおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "岩崎", "answers": [ "いわさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小倉", "answers": [ "おぐら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "村田", "answers": [ "むらた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "大谷", "answers": [ "おおたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "小沢", "answers": [ "おざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "小笠原", "answers": [ "おがさわら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "西川", "answers": [ "にしかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "大田", "answers": [ "おおた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%" },
	{ "question": "川口", "answers": [ "かわぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%" },
	{ "question": "杉山", "answers": [ "すぎやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "平田", "answers": [ "ひらた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "石橋", "answers": [ "いしばし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "康", "answers": [ "かん", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "飯田", "answers": [ "いいだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%" },
	{ "question": "三宅", "answers": [ "みやけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "河野", "answers": [ "こうの", "かわの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "北条", "answers": [ "ほうじょう", "きたじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "荒木", "answers": [ "あらき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "牧野", "answers": [ "まきの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "王", "answers": [ "おう", "ワン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "松浦", "answers": [ "まつうら", "まつら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "呉", "answers": [ "ご", "くれ", "オ", "ヴァネス" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%, 9%, 6%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "服部", "answers": [ "はっとり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "白石", "answers": [ "しらいし", "しろいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "秋山", "answers": [ "あきやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "谷", "answers": [ "たに", "こく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "長岡", "answers": [ "ながおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 27%" },
	{ "question": "熊谷", "answers": [ "くまがい", "くまがや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "川島", "answers": [ "かわしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "稔", "answers": [ "みのる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "三島", "answers": [ "みしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%" },
	{ "question": "成田", "answers": [ "なりた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%" },
	{ "question": "川上", "answers": [ "かわかみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "佐伯", "answers": [ "さえき", "さいき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "泉", "answers": [ "いずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%" },
	{ "question": "矢野", "answers": [ "やの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "美穂", "answers": [ "みほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "稲葉", "answers": [ "いなば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "本田", "answers": [ "ほんだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "安倍", "answers": [ "あべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "片岡", "answers": [ "かたおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "小池", "answers": [ "こいけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小西", "answers": [ "こにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "神田", "answers": [ "かんだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "大橋", "answers": [ "おおはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "丸山", "answers": [ "まるやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "大石", "answers": [ "おおいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "大津", "answers": [ "おおつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "立川", "answers": [ "たてかわ", "たちかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "中西", "answers": [ "なかにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻生", "answers": [ "あそう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "篠原", "answers": [ "しのはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "北村", "answers": [ "きたむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "堀内", "answers": [ "ほりうち", "ほりのうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "平井", "answers": [ "ひらい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "手塚", "answers": [ "てづか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "辻", "answers": [ "つじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中原", "answers": [ "なかはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "陳", "answers": [ "ちん", "チェン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "土井", "answers": [ "どい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "高島", "answers": [ "たかしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%" },
	{ "question": "大山", "answers": [ "おおやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "高崎", "answers": [ "たかさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "新井", "answers": [ "あらい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "荒川", "answers": [ "あらかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%" },
	{ "question": "金田", "answers": [ "かねだ", "かなだ", "かねた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 13%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "藤沢", "answers": [ "ふじさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 32%" },
	{ "question": "三好", "answers": [ "みよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%" },
	{ "question": "土屋", "answers": [ "つちや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由美", "answers": [ "ゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "西尾", "answers": [ "にしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%" },
	{ "question": "堀江", "answers": [ "ほりえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "秦", "answers": [ "はた", "しん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "上原", "answers": [ "うえはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "真田", "answers": [ "さなだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "大村", "answers": [ "おおむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "恵", "answers": [ "めぐみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "吉野", "answers": [ "よしの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%" },
	{ "question": "高野", "answers": [ "たかの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "倉敷", "answers": [ "くらしき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "沢田", "answers": [ "さわだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "奥田", "answers": [ "おくだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "飯塚", "answers": [ "いいづか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "椎名", "answers": [ "しいな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "足立", "answers": [ "あだち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%" },
	{ "question": "日野", "answers": [ "ひの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%" },
	{ "question": "梅田", "answers": [ "うめだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 36%" },
	{ "question": "川村", "answers": [ "かわむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "松原", "answers": [ "まつばら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "小室", "answers": [ "こむろ", "おもろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "天野", "answers": [ "あまの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "町田", "answers": [ "まちだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%" },
	{ "question": "坂口", "answers": [ "さかぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "結城", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "田辺", "answers": [ "たなべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "松下", "answers": [ "まつした" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "増田", "answers": [ "ますだ", "ました" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "谷口", "answers": [ "たにぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佐竹", "answers": [ "さたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "中尾", "answers": [ "なかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "五十嵐", "answers": [ "いがらし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "函館", "answers": [ "はこだて" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "久保", "answers": [ "くぼ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "久保田", "answers": [ "くぼた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "南部", "answers": [ "なんぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "瞳", "answers": [ "ひとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "水谷", "answers": [ "みずたに", "みずのや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "野口", "answers": [ "のぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "松村", "answers": [ "まつむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "萩原", "answers": [ "はぎわら", "はぎはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "田口", "answers": [ "たぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小田", "answers": [ "おだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "藤岡", "answers": [ "ふじおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "三田", "answers": [ "みた", "さんだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "大森", "answers": [ "おおもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "佐久間", "answers": [ "さくま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "樋口", "answers": [ "ひぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "永田", "answers": [ "ながた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "高岡", "answers": [ "たかおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%" },
	{ "question": "曹", "answers": [ "そう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中井", "answers": [ "なかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "大友", "answers": [ "おおとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寺田", "answers": [ "てらだ", "てらた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "富田", "answers": [ "とみた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "大川", "answers": [ "おおかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "渡部", "answers": [ "わたなべ", "わたべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%, 35%" },
	{ "question": "水戸", "answers": [ "みと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "岡村", "answers": [ "おかむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "緒方", "answers": [ "おがた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "森山", "answers": [ "もりやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "岩田", "answers": [ "いわた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "豊島", "answers": [ "とよしま", "としま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "目黒", "answers": [ "めぐろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "杉本", "answers": [ "すぎもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "片山", "answers": [ "かたやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "八代", "answers": [ "やしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%" },
	{ "question": "有馬", "answers": [ "ありま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "村山", "answers": [ "むらやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "吉村", "answers": [ "よしむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "古川", "answers": [ "ふるかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "藤村", "answers": [ "ふじむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "稲垣", "answers": [ "いながき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鶴岡", "answers": [ "つるおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%" },
	{ "question": "榊原", "answers": [ "さかきばら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "北", "answers": [ "きた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%" },
	{ "question": "広瀬", "answers": [ "ひろせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "畠山", "answers": [ "はたけやま", "はたやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "松永", "answers": [ "まつなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "西宮", "answers": [ "にしみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "岸", "answers": [ "きし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "飯島", "answers": [ "いいじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "大沢", "answers": [ "おおさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "明石", "answers": [ "あかし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%" },
	{ "question": "松任谷", "answers": [ "まつとうや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和泉", "answers": [ "いずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%" },
	{ "question": "日高", "answers": [ "ひだか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%" },
	{ "question": "八戸", "answers": [ "はちのへ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "関根", "answers": [ "せきね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "三原", "answers": [ "みはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%" },
	{ "question": "桑田", "answers": [ "くわた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "津田", "answers": [ "つだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "川越", "answers": [ "かわごえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "鎌倉", "answers": [ "かまくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "田原", "answers": [ "たはら", "たばら", "たわら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 10%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "北原", "answers": [ "きたはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "筒井", "answers": [ "つつい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "新田", "answers": [ "にった" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "大江", "answers": [ "おおえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "坂井", "answers": [ "さかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "森川", "answers": [ "もりかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宇野", "answers": [ "うの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "河合", "answers": [ "かわい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "北川", "answers": [ "きたがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "横須賀", "answers": [ "よこすか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "菅野", "answers": [ "かんの", "すがの", "すげの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 17%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "森下", "answers": [ "もりした" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "江戸川", "answers": [ "えどがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%" },
	{ "question": "水木", "answers": [ "みずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "美里", "answers": [ "みさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "鳩山", "answers": [ "はとやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "武藤", "answers": [ "むとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山中", "answers": [ "やまなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "平山", "answers": [ "ひらやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "大竹", "answers": [ "おおたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "大木", "answers": [ "おおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%" },
	{ "question": "松江", "answers": [ "まつえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "栗原", "answers": [ "くりはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%" },
	{ "question": "星", "answers": [ "ほし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "周", "answers": [ "しゅう", "ジョウ", "ヴィック", "チャウ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 4%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "水島", "answers": [ "みずしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "浜崎", "answers": [ "はまさき", "はまざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "信夫", "answers": [ "しのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "八木", "answers": [ "やぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "櫻井", "answers": [ "さくらい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朝倉", "answers": [ "あさくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%" },
	{ "question": "岸田", "answers": [ "きしだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "章", "answers": [ "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "板橋", "answers": [ "いたばし", "いたはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "笑福亭", "answers": [ "しょうふくてい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夏目", "answers": [ "なつめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊勢", "answers": [ "いせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "小田原", "answers": [ "おだわら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "博多", "answers": [ "はかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "船橋", "answers": [ "ふなばし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "亀井", "answers": [ "かめい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "児玉", "answers": [ "こだま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "森本", "answers": [ "もりもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "谷川", "answers": [ "たにがわ", "たにかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 42%" },
	{ "question": "古賀", "answers": [ "こが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "元", "answers": [ "はじめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "望月", "answers": [ "もちづき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弘前", "answers": [ "ひろさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "立花", "answers": [ "たちばな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "橘", "answers": [ "たちばな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "若林", "answers": [ "わかばやし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "大内", "answers": [ "おおうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "大西", "answers": [ "おおにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "川田", "answers": [ "かわだ", "かわた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "杉浦", "answers": [ "すぎうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大和", "answers": [ "やまと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "柳沢", "answers": [ "やなぎさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "落合", "answers": [ "おちあい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "坂田", "answers": [ "さかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "志村", "answers": [ "しむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "真弓", "answers": [ "まゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "吉岡", "answers": [ "よしおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "東野", "answers": [ "ひがしの", "とうの", "あずまの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 41%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "鶴田", "answers": [ "つるた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%" },
	{ "question": "今川", "answers": [ "いまがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "杉田", "answers": [ "すぎた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "岡部", "answers": [ "おかべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "古田", "answers": [ "ふるた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "西郷", "answers": [ "さいごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "西", "answers": [ "にし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "北島", "answers": [ "きたじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "小坂", "answers": [ "こさか", "おさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "大原", "answers": [ "おおはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "一樹", "answers": [ "いつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "市原", "answers": [ "いちはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%" },
	{ "question": "浅田", "answers": [ "あさだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "京極", "answers": [ "きょうごく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "難波", "answers": [ "なんば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%" },
	{ "question": "菊地", "answers": [ "きくち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "坂上", "answers": [ "さかがみ", "さかのうえ", "さかじょう", "さかうえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 37%, 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "宮田", "answers": [ "みやた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "二宮", "answers": [ "にのみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "黒木", "answers": [ "くろき", "くろぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "早川", "answers": [ "はやかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "亀山", "answers": [ "かめやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%" },
	{ "question": "徳永", "answers": [ "とくなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "伊丹", "answers": [ "いたみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%" },
	{ "question": "橋上", "answers": [ "はしがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "竹中", "answers": [ "たけなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "中", "answers": [ "なか", "あたり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "麻美", "answers": [ "あさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "風間", "answers": [ "かざま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "大崎", "answers": [ "おおさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "竹田", "answers": [ "たけだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "神谷", "answers": [ "かみや", "かみたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "別府", "answers": [ "べっぷ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 32%" },
	{ "question": "柏", "answers": [ "かしわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "真理", "answers": [ "まり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "中嶋", "answers": [ "なかじま", "なかしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "白井", "answers": [ "しらい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "美樹", "answers": [ "みき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "赤松", "answers": [ "あかまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "江川", "answers": [ "えがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "滝沢", "answers": [ "たきざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%" },
	{ "question": "黒澤", "answers": [ "くろさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春日", "answers": [ "かすが", "はるひ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "瑞穂", "answers": [ "みずほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "三上", "answers": [ "みかみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "利根川", "answers": [ "とねがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "大垣", "answers": [ "おおがき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "梶原", "answers": [ "かじわら", "かじはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "榎本", "answers": [ "えのもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "丹羽", "answers": [ "にわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "板倉", "answers": [ "いたくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "野沢", "answers": [ "のざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "大宮", "answers": [ "おおみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "旭", "answers": [ "あさひ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "日向", "answers": [ "ひなた", "ひゅうが", "ひむかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%, 23%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "瀬戸", "answers": [ "せと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%" },
	{ "question": "有田", "answers": [ "ありた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%" },
	{ "question": "志賀", "answers": [ "しが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "安部", "answers": [ "あべ", "あんべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "関口", "answers": [ "せきぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "西岡", "answers": [ "にしおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "一宮", "answers": [ "いちみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "野中", "answers": [ "のなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "堤", "answers": [ "つつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "葉山", "answers": [ "はやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%" },
	{ "question": "竹下", "answers": [ "たけした" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "角田", "answers": [ "つのだ", "かくた", "かくだ", "すみだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%, 19%, 16%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "今村", "answers": [ "いまむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石塚", "answers": [ "いしづか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "植田", "answers": [ "うえだ", "うえた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "矢島", "answers": [ "やじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "根岸", "answers": [ "ねぎし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "井伊", "answers": [ "いい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中森", "answers": [ "なかもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "赤坂", "answers": [ "あかさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%" },
	{ "question": "加賀", "answers": [ "かが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%" },
	{ "question": "安達", "answers": [ "あだち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "長尾", "answers": [ "ながお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "柏原", "answers": [ "かしわばら", "かしはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "松戸", "answers": [ "まつど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "寺島", "answers": [ "てらしま", "てらじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 34%" },
	{ "question": "桐生", "answers": [ "きりゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "岡野", "answers": [ "おかの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松坂", "answers": [ "まつざか", "まつさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "豊臣", "answers": [ "とよとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "相馬", "answers": [ "そうま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%" },
	{ "question": "岩本", "answers": [ "いわもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "吹田", "answers": [ "すいた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "平塚", "answers": [ "ひらつか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "溝口", "answers": [ "みぞぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "福原", "answers": [ "ふくはら", "ふくばら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "墨田", "answers": [ "すみだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "村松", "answers": [ "むらまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "文", "answers": [ "ぶん", "ムン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "沼田", "answers": [ "ぬまた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%" },
	{ "question": "本間", "answers": [ "ほんま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "諏訪", "answers": [ "すわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%" },
	{ "question": "津山", "answers": [ "つやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "豊川", "answers": [ "とよかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "羽田", "answers": [ "はねだ", "はた", "はだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%, 35%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "岡", "answers": [ "おか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "小杉", "answers": [ "こすぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "堀田", "answers": [ "ほった", "ほりた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "篠田", "answers": [ "しのだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "細野", "answers": [ "ほその" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "内海", "answers": [ "うつみ", "うちうみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "宮沢", "answers": [ "みやざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久喜", "answers": [ "きゅうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "小牧", "answers": [ "こまき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 24%" },
	{ "question": "高槻", "answers": [ "たかつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "馬場", "answers": [ "ばば", "ばんば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "畑", "answers": [ "はた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "香取", "answers": [ "かとり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%" },
	{ "question": "江口", "answers": [ "えぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "那須", "answers": [ "なす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "蒋", "answers": [ "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鍋島", "answers": [ "なべしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "谷村", "answers": [ "たにむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "袁", "answers": [ "えん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "丹波", "answers": [ "たんば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "西山", "answers": [ "にしやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "根本", "answers": [ "ねもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "平松", "answers": [ "ひらまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "浅井", "answers": [ "あさい", "あざい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "益田", "answers": [ "ますだ", "ました" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "山川", "answers": [ "やまかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "清原", "answers": [ "きよはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "柳田", "answers": [ "やなぎた", "やなぎだ", "やなだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%, 47%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "掛川", "answers": [ "かけがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "鄭", "answers": [ "てい", "チョン", "ジェン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 33%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "多田", "answers": [ "ただ", "おおた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "松島", "answers": [ "まつしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%" },
	{ "question": "内山", "answers": [ "うちやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "白鳥", "answers": [ "しらとり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "川端", "answers": [ "かわばた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "土岐", "answers": [ "とき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%" },
	{ "question": "田代", "answers": [ "たしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "須藤", "answers": [ "すどう", "すとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "河村", "answers": [ "かわむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "里見", "answers": [ "さとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "桑名", "answers": [ "くわな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "遥", "answers": [ "はるか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "長浜", "answers": [ "ながはま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "甲斐", "answers": [ "かい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%" },
	{ "question": "新庄", "answers": [ "しんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%" },
	{ "question": "福永", "answers": [ "ふくなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大平", "answers": [ "おおひら", "たいへい", "おおだいら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 15%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "松阪", "answers": [ "まつざか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "成瀬", "answers": [ "なるせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "水原", "answers": [ "みずはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "藤堂", "answers": [ "とうどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "江原", "answers": [ "えばら", "えはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "明石家", "answers": [ "あかしや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "速水", "answers": [ "はやみ", "はやみず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "豊岡", "answers": [ "とよおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "村井", "answers": [ "むらい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "狩野", "answers": [ "かのう", "かの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 26%" },
	{ "question": "荒井", "answers": [ "あらい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "趙", "answers": [ "ちょう", "チョ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "三遊亭", "answers": [ "さんゆうてい", "さんゆうてう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "滝川", "answers": [ "たきがわ", "たきかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "菅", "answers": [ "すが", "かん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "高", "answers": [ "こう", "コ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "新", "answers": [ "あたらし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "茨木", "answers": [ "いばらき", "いばらぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "江藤", "answers": [ "えとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "北見", "answers": [ "きたみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%" },
	{ "question": "東郷", "answers": [ "とうごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "神山", "answers": [ "かみやま", "こうやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "涼", "answers": [ "すずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "国府", "answers": [ "こくぶ", "こくふ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "政宗", "answers": [ "まさむね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "本郷", "answers": [ "ほんごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "青島", "answers": [ "あおしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%" },
	{ "question": "安井", "answers": [ "やすい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "中谷", "answers": [ "なかたに", "なかや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "上村", "answers": [ "うえむら", "かみむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "島", "answers": [ "しま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "山名", "answers": [ "やまな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "寿", "answers": [ "ことぶき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "塚本", "answers": [ "つかもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "下田", "answers": [ "しもだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%" },
	{ "question": "出雲", "answers": [ "いずもの", "いずも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "及川", "answers": [ "おいかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大岡", "answers": [ "おおおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "五木", "answers": [ "いつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "倉田", "answers": [ "くらた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "聖", "answers": [ "ひじり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "黒沢", "answers": [ "くろさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "米原", "answers": [ "よねはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "大林", "answers": [ "おおばやし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "本庄", "answers": [ "ほんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%" },
	{ "question": "楊", "answers": [ "よう", "ヤン", "やん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 8%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "富士", "answers": [ "ふじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "鳥羽", "answers": [ "とば", "とりば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 32%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "高瀬", "answers": [ "たかせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "対馬", "answers": [ "つしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "小原", "answers": [ "おはら", "おばら", "こはら", "こばら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 25%, 14%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "伊賀", "answers": [ "いが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "石巻", "answers": [ "いしまき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "白川", "answers": [ "しらかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%" },
	{ "question": "遠山", "answers": [ "とおやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宮川", "answers": [ "みやがわ", "みやかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 35%" },
	{ "question": "前川", "answers": [ "まえかわ", "まえがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "山村", "answers": [ "やまむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "松野", "answers": [ "まつの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "植村", "answers": [ "うえむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "明智", "answers": [ "あけち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "朴", "answers": [ "パク", "ぼく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "石坂", "answers": [ "いしざか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "鳥居", "answers": [ "とりい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "宮下", "answers": [ "みやした" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "横手", "answers": [ "よこて" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "奥村", "answers": [ "おくむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梅津", "answers": [ "うめづ", "うめつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "林家", "answers": [ "はやしや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "司", "answers": [ "つかさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 27%" },
	{ "question": "唐沢", "answers": [ "からさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桃井", "answers": [ "ももい", "もものい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "宮澤", "answers": [ "みやざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "西城", "answers": [ "さいじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "福本", "answers": [ "ふくもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "西野", "answers": [ "にしの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "小平", "answers": [ "こだいら", "おだいら", "こひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 27%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "佐倉", "answers": [ "さくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 32%" },
	{ "question": "米沢", "answers": [ "よねざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "新城", "answers": [ "あらしろ", "しんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "古谷", "answers": [ "ふるや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "由紀", "answers": [ "ゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%" },
	{ "question": "平泉", "answers": [ "ひらいずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%" },
	{ "question": "大槻", "answers": [ "おおつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "阿南", "answers": [ "あなみ", "あなん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "栗山", "answers": [ "くりやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "米倉", "answers": [ "よねくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "生駒", "answers": [ "いこま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 44%" },
	{ "question": "板垣", "answers": [ "いたがき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山根", "answers": [ "やまね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美咲", "answers": [ "みさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "小澤", "answers": [ "おざわ", "こざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "新宮", "answers": [ "しんぐう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "山寺", "answers": [ "やまでら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "福澤", "answers": [ "ふくざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "野島", "answers": [ "のじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "桜", "answers": [ "さくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%" },
	{ "question": "山岡", "answers": [ "やまおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "田島", "answers": [ "たじま", "たしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "稲田", "answers": [ "いなだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "金山", "answers": [ "かなやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%" },
	{ "question": "井口", "answers": [ "いぐち", "いのくち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "唯", "answers": [ "ゆい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "朱", "answers": [ "しゅ", "ケン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "暁", "answers": [ "あかつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "亘", "answers": [ "わたり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "歩", "answers": [ "ほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "桑原", "answers": [ "くわばら", "くわはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 27%" },
	{ "question": "深谷", "answers": [ "ふかや", "ふかたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "土田", "answers": [ "つちだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "今野", "answers": [ "こんの", "いまの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "石黒", "answers": [ "いしぐろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "羽生", "answers": [ "はぶ", "はにゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "松崎", "answers": [ "まつざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "一色", "answers": [ "いっしき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "蜂須賀", "answers": [ "はちすか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長門", "answers": [ "ながと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%" },
	{ "question": "武内", "answers": [ "たけうち", "たけうちのすくね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "鶴見", "answers": [ "つるみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%" },
	{ "question": "亀田", "answers": [ "かめだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "津島", "answers": [ "つしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%" },
	{ "question": "若松", "answers": [ "わかまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "渋川", "answers": [ "しぶかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%" },
	{ "question": "大杉", "answers": [ "おおすぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "井原", "answers": [ "いはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%" },
	{ "question": "倖田", "answers": [ "こうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "岩井", "answers": [ "いわい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "龍", "answers": [ "りゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "黒川", "answers": [ "くろかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "明日香", "answers": [ "あすか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "陣内", "answers": [ "じんない", "じんのうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "桜田", "answers": [ "さくらだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "千秋", "answers": [ "ちあき", "せんしゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "黄", "answers": [ "こう", "ファン", "ホヮン", "ホアン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 13%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "宮内", "answers": [ "みやうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "内村", "answers": [ "うちむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "島崎", "answers": [ "しまざき", "しまさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "五島", "answers": [ "ごとう", "ごしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "柳生", "answers": [ "やぎゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "阿久", "answers": [ "あく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大月", "answers": [ "おおつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%" },
	{ "question": "三条", "answers": [ "さんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "研", "answers": [ "けん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%" },
	{ "question": "司馬", "answers": [ "しば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "日本橋", "answers": [ "にほんばし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "綾瀬", "answers": [ "あやせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%" },
	{ "question": "湯浅", "answers": [ "ゆあさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "筒美", "answers": [ "つつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "池上", "answers": [ "いけがみ", "いけうえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "齋藤", "answers": [ "さいとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小柳", "answers": [ "こやなぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "和久", "answers": [ "わく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "厚木", "answers": [ "あつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "吉井", "answers": [ "よしい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "中澤", "answers": [ "なかざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晶", "answers": [ "あきら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "河本", "answers": [ "こうもと", "かわもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "名取", "answers": [ "なとり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%" },
	{ "question": "西原", "answers": [ "にしはら", "さいばら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "矢沢", "answers": [ "やざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "中津", "answers": [ "なかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "富岡", "answers": [ "とみおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%" },
	{ "question": "峰", "answers": [ "みね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "入江", "answers": [ "いりえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "横田", "answers": [ "よこた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "所", "answers": [ "ところ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竜", "answers": [ "りゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%" },
	{ "question": "馬", "answers": [ "ば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "紀", "answers": [ "き", "きの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "犬山", "answers": [ "いぬやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "伊集院", "answers": [ "いじゅういん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "尚", "answers": [ "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "草野", "answers": [ "くさの", "そうの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "布施", "answers": [ "ふせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "美空", "answers": [ "みそら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "小早川", "answers": [ "こばやかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "青野", "answers": [ "あおの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "葵", "answers": [ "あおい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "大和田", "answers": [ "おおわだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "庄司", "answers": [ "しょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "白山", "answers": [ "しらやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "岩倉", "answers": [ "いわくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%" },
	{ "question": "皆川", "answers": [ "みながわ", "みなかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "夏川", "answers": [ "なつかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "平川", "answers": [ "ひらかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%" },
	{ "question": "加瀬", "answers": [ "かせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "未来", "answers": [ "みらい", "みき", "みく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%, 4%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "塚田", "answers": [ "つかだ", "つかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "太", "answers": [ "おお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "新橋", "answers": [ "しんばし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "大泉", "answers": [ "おおいずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%" },
	{ "question": "泰", "answers": [ "たい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "幸", "answers": [ "みゆき", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "柳", "answers": [ "やなぎ", "ユ", "ゆう", "りゅう", "リュ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 10%, 10%, 7%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "湯沢", "answers": [ "ゆざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "平岡", "answers": [ "ひらおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "小森", "answers": [ "こもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "植木", "answers": [ "うえき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "中津川", "answers": [ "なかつがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "柳川", "answers": [ "やながわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%" },
	{ "question": "藤山", "answers": [ "ふじやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "高杉", "answers": [ "たかすぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "北野", "answers": [ "きたの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%" },
	{ "question": "大場", "answers": [ "おおば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "七尾", "answers": [ "ななお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "川西", "answers": [ "かわにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "石野", "answers": [ "いしの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "秩父", "answers": [ "ちちぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "六本木", "answers": [ "ろっぽんぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "萩", "answers": [ "はぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "片桐", "answers": [ "かたぎり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "藤森", "answers": [ "ふじもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "影山", "answers": [ "かげやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "永野", "answers": [ "ながの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "向井", "answers": [ "むかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "水樹", "answers": [ "みずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三沢", "answers": [ "みさわ", "みざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "岩城", "answers": [ "いわき", "いわしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "吉良", "answers": [ "きら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "黒部", "answers": [ "くろべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%" },
	{ "question": "土方", "answers": [ "ひじかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "霧島", "answers": [ "きりしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%" },
	{ "question": "笠原", "answers": [ "かさはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "柏崎", "answers": [ "かしわざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "吉永", "answers": [ "よしなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "伊勢崎", "answers": [ "いせざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "岸本", "answers": [ "きしもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "茂木", "answers": [ "もぎ", "もてぎ", "しげき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 14%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "渡邉", "answers": [ "わたなべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石ノ森", "answers": [ "いしのもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長澤", "answers": [ "ながさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "新垣", "answers": [ "あらがき", "にいがき", "あらかき", "しんがき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 44%, 23%, 18%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "東山", "answers": [ "ひがしやま", "とうやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "芥川", "answers": [ "あくたがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "愛川", "answers": [ "あいかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "遠野", "answers": [ "とおの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 36%" },
	{ "question": "矢部", "answers": [ "やべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "能登", "answers": [ "のと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "河内", "answers": [ "かわち", "こうち", "かわうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 44%, 19%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "鎌田", "answers": [ "かまた", "かまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "長田", "answers": [ "おさだ", "ながた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "佐渡", "answers": [ "さど", "さわたり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "林原", "answers": [ "はやしばら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宇治", "answers": [ "うじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "杉", "answers": [ "すぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "玄田", "answers": [ "げんだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三村", "answers": [ "みむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "西条", "answers": [ "さいじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "藤", "answers": [ "ふじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "新谷", "answers": [ "しんたに", "しんや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "玉置", "answers": [ "たまき", "たまおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "国分", "answers": [ "こくぶん", "こくぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "韓", "answers": [ "かん", "ハン", "はん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 17%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "松前", "answers": [ "まつまえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%" },
	{ "question": "長井", "answers": [ "ながい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%" },
	{ "question": "栗林", "answers": [ "くりばやし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "久", "answers": [ "ひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "幸田", "answers": [ "こうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%" },
	{ "question": "加山", "answers": [ "かやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "古河", "answers": [ "ふるかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "早乙女", "answers": [ "さおとめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春日井", "answers": [ "かすがい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "重信", "answers": [ "しげのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "濱田", "answers": [ "はまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "七瀬", "answers": [ "ななせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%" },
	{ "question": "穂積", "answers": [ "ほづみ", "ほずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "安室", "answers": [ "あむろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "都城", "answers": [ "みやしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "諸葛", "answers": [ "しょかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "川本", "answers": [ "かわもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "三宮", "answers": [ "さんみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "渚", "answers": [ "なぎさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%" },
	{ "question": "藤枝", "answers": [ "ふじえだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 27%" },
	{ "question": "吉原", "answers": [ "よしはら", "よしわら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "水上", "answers": [ "みずかみ", "みなかみ", "みかみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 27%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "美保", "answers": [ "みほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%" },
	{ "question": "有紀", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "有川", "answers": [ "ありかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久米", "answers": [ "くめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "花巻", "answers": [ "はなまき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "竹本", "answers": [ "たけもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鮎川", "answers": [ "あゆかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "銚子", "answers": [ "ちょうし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "毛", "answers": [ "もう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "園田", "answers": [ "そのだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌子", "answers": [ "しょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "亀岡", "answers": [ "かめおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "渡", "answers": [ "わたり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%" },
	{ "question": "矢口", "answers": [ "やぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "最上", "answers": [ "もがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "呂", "answers": [ "りょ", "ヨ", "ルー", "ル" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 5%, 4%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "坪井", "answers": [ "つぼい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "相沢", "answers": [ "あいざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "納谷", "answers": [ "なや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "北畠", "answers": [ "きたばたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "楠", "answers": [ "くすのき", "くす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "新発田", "answers": [ "しばた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "川原", "answers": [ "かわはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "乾", "answers": [ "いぬい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "我孫子", "answers": [ "あびこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "小栗", "answers": [ "おぐり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石丸", "answers": [ "いしまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鈴鹿", "answers": [ "すずか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "三谷", "answers": [ "みたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "深川", "answers": [ "ふかがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "湯川", "answers": [ "ゆかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "大河内", "answers": [ "おおこうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "西脇", "answers": [ "にしわき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%" },
	{ "question": "小出", "answers": [ "こいで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "久美", "answers": [ "くみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "小谷", "answers": [ "こたに", "おだに", "おたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 6%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "藍", "answers": [ "あい", "らん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "海老名", "answers": [ "えびな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%" },
	{ "question": "半田", "answers": [ "はんだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 32%" },
	{ "question": "東海", "answers": [ "とうかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "大町", "answers": [ "おおまち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "一条", "answers": [ "いちじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "辰巳", "answers": [ "たつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%" },
	{ "question": "輪島", "answers": [ "わじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%" },
	{ "question": "要", "answers": [ "かなめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "二階堂", "answers": [ "にかいどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "大地", "answers": [ "だいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "志摩", "answers": [ "しま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "堂本", "answers": [ "どうもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小宮", "answers": [ "こみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "川内", "answers": [ "かわうち", "かわち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "子安", "answers": [ "こやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "小山田", "answers": [ "おやまだ", "こやまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "相川", "answers": [ "あいかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "神崎", "answers": [ "かんざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "折笠", "answers": [ "おりかさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "安", "answers": [ "やす", "アン", "あん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%, 26%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "松方", "answers": [ "まつかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "草津", "answers": [ "くさつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "松", "answers": [ "まつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "宍戸", "answers": [ "ししど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "木内", "answers": [ "きうち", "きのうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "白河", "answers": [ "しらかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "斯波", "answers": [ "しば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "藤木", "answers": [ "ふじき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "沢村", "answers": [ "さわむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "保", "answers": [ "たもつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "相良", "answers": [ "さがら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "谷山", "answers": [ "たにやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "太宰", "answers": [ "だざい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "西本", "answers": [ "にしもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高津", "answers": [ "こうづ", "たかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 45%" },
	{ "question": "柏木", "answers": [ "かしわぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大井", "answers": [ "おおい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%" },
	{ "question": "川勝", "answers": [ "かわかつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美郷", "answers": [ "みさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "津川", "answers": [ "つがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "神保", "answers": [ "じんぼ", "じんぼう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "天王寺", "answers": [ "てんのうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "佐々", "answers": [ "さっさ", "ささ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "北山", "answers": [ "きたやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%" },
	{ "question": "都", "answers": [ "みやこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%" },
	{ "question": "冨田", "answers": [ "とみた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "南原", "answers": [ "なんばら", "みなみはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "新藤", "answers": [ "しんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "多治見", "answers": [ "たじみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "塩尻", "answers": [ "しおじり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "緑川", "answers": [ "みどりかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "郭", "answers": [ "かく", "カク" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "仲村", "answers": [ "なかむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千田", "answers": [ "せんだ", "ちだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 27%" },
	{ "question": "清川", "answers": [ "きよかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "馬飼野", "answers": [ "まかいの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "栗田", "answers": [ "くりた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "梶", "answers": [ "かじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "館山", "answers": [ "たてやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "塩屋", "answers": [ "しおや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "別所", "answers": [ "べっしょ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "石垣", "answers": [ "いしがき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%" },
	{ "question": "生田", "answers": [ "いくた", "しょうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "浅倉", "answers": [ "あさくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "尼子", "answers": [ "あまご", "あまこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "藤崎", "answers": [ "ふじさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "高村", "answers": [ "たかむら", "こうむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 27%" },
	{ "question": "鹿島", "answers": [ "かしま", "かじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "陸", "answers": [ "りく", "くが", "ユク" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 9%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "石岡", "answers": [ "いしおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "西園寺", "answers": [ "さいおんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中曽根", "answers": [ "なかそね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "杉原", "answers": [ "すぎはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "三船", "answers": [ "みふね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "平尾", "answers": [ "ひらお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "五月", "answers": [ "さつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%" },
	{ "question": "宋", "answers": [ "そう", "ソン", "そん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 10%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "今田", "answers": [ "いまだ", "こんた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "下村", "answers": [ "しもむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "左", "answers": [ "ひだり", "さ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "綾部", "answers": [ "あやべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%" },
	{ "question": "吉本", "answers": [ "よしもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長渕", "answers": [ "ながぶち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宇多田", "answers": [ "うただ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "堀川", "answers": [ "ほりかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "戸塚", "answers": [ "とつか", "とづか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "伊吹", "answers": [ "いぶき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "高畑", "answers": [ "たかはた", "たかばたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "久志", "answers": [ "くし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "芦田", "answers": [ "あしだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朝日", "answers": [ "あさひ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "蜷川", "answers": [ "にながわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "越前", "answers": [ "えちぜん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "胡", "answers": [ "こ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "仁志", "answers": [ "にし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "窪田", "answers": [ "くぼた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沖田", "answers": [ "おきた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "熊野", "answers": [ "くまの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "京", "answers": [ "きょう", "けい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "渡瀬", "answers": [ "わたせ", "わたらせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "諫早", "answers": [ "いさはや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "吉見", "answers": [ "よしみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%" },
	{ "question": "安西", "answers": [ "あんざい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "楠木", "answers": [ "くすのき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "笛吹", "answers": [ "うすい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "森岡", "answers": [ "もりおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "円谷", "answers": [ "つぶらや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "北上", "answers": [ "きたがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "有吉", "answers": [ "ありよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "真琴", "answers": [ "まこと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%" },
	{ "question": "山岸", "answers": [ "やまぎし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "南野", "answers": [ "みなみの", "のおの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "東條", "answers": [ "とうじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大貫", "answers": [ "おおぬき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "池内", "answers": [ "いけうち", "いけのうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "加茂", "answers": [ "かも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%" },
	{ "question": "三輪", "answers": [ "みわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "菊川", "answers": [ "きくかわ", "きくがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "遊佐", "answers": [ "ゆさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%" },
	{ "question": "鳥海", "answers": [ "とりうみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "中居", "answers": [ "なかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "武部", "answers": [ "たけべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奥平", "answers": [ "おくだいら", "おくひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "児島", "answers": [ "こじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%" },
	{ "question": "城", "answers": [ "じょう", "きずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "加納", "answers": [ "かのう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "崔", "answers": [ "チェ", "さい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "布袋", "answers": [ "ほてい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "早見", "answers": [ "はやみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "深田", "answers": [ "ふかだ", "ふかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "上山", "answers": [ "うえやま", "かみやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "五味", "answers": [ "ごみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "淡路", "answers": [ "あわじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%" },
	{ "question": "野坂", "answers": [ "のさか", "のざか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "伴", "answers": [ "ばん", "とも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "原口", "answers": [ "はらぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "金森", "answers": [ "かなもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "蘇我", "answers": [ "そが", "そがの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "甲賀", "answers": [ "こうが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "麻里", "answers": [ "あさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "大黒", "answers": [ "おおぐろ", "だいこく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "下川", "answers": [ "しもかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%" },
	{ "question": "蒲生", "answers": [ "がもう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "鉄矢", "answers": [ "てつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "大倉", "answers": [ "おおくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "赤羽", "answers": [ "あかば", "あかばね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "八幡", "answers": [ "やわた", "やはた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "高見", "answers": [ "たかみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "葛西", "answers": [ "かさい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "成", "answers": [ "せい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "嶋田", "answers": [ "しまだ", "しまた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "貝塚", "answers": [ "かいづか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "建", "answers": [ "たて" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "矢吹", "answers": [ "やぶき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%" },
	{ "question": "川合", "answers": [ "かわい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "刈谷", "answers": [ "かりや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "小浜", "answers": [ "こはま", "おはま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "六角", "answers": [ "ろっかく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "渋沢", "answers": [ "しぶさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "茅野", "answers": [ "かやの", "ちの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "日南", "answers": [ "ひなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "森永", "answers": [ "もりなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "新川", "answers": [ "しんかわ", "にいかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "衣笠", "answers": [ "きぬがさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "中条", "answers": [ "なかじょう", "ちゅうじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%, 40%" },
	{ "question": "金井", "answers": [ "かない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "八雲", "answers": [ "やくも", "やぐも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "葉月", "answers": [ "はづき", "はつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "小野寺", "answers": [ "おのでら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "瀬戸内", "answers": [ "せとうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "大田原", "answers": [ "おおたわら", "おおたはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "本山", "answers": [ "もとやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "玉川", "answers": [ "たまがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "立木", "answers": [ "たちき", "たつき", "たき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 8%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "高浜", "answers": [ "たかはま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%" },
	{ "question": "須田", "answers": [ "すだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小渕", "answers": [ "おぶち", "こぶち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "貴志", "answers": [ "きし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "高井", "answers": [ "たかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "下野", "answers": [ "しもの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%" },
	{ "question": "山路", "answers": [ "やまじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久松", "answers": [ "ひさまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "牧", "answers": [ "まき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "椿", "answers": [ "つばき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "黒崎", "answers": [ "くろさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "一柳", "answers": [ "ひとつやなぎ", "いちやなぎ", "いちりゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 20%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "伊豆", "answers": [ "いず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "漣", "answers": [ "さざなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "野川", "answers": [ "のがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田川", "answers": [ "たがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%" },
	{ "question": "勝浦", "answers": [ "かつうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "渡邊", "answers": [ "わたなべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浅川", "answers": [ "あさかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "谷崎", "answers": [ "たにざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仁科", "answers": [ "にしな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "咲", "answers": [ "さき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "寺尾", "answers": [ "てらお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "釘宮", "answers": [ "くぎみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奈美", "answers": [ "なみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%" },
	{ "question": "肝付", "answers": [ "きもつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "置鮎", "answers": [ "おきあゆ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武蔵", "answers": [ "むさし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "長島", "answers": [ "ながしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%" },
	{ "question": "久慈", "answers": [ "くじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 27%" },
	{ "question": "宮脇", "answers": [ "みやわき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "中沢", "answers": [ "なかざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "茅ヶ崎", "answers": [ "ちがさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "平沼", "answers": [ "ひらぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "田上", "answers": [ "たがみ", "たうえ", "たのうえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%, 29%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "外山", "answers": [ "とやま", "そとやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "上川", "answers": [ "かみかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%" },
	{ "question": "柳原", "answers": [ "やなぎはら", "やなぎわら", "やなはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 18%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "的場", "answers": [ "まとば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "槇原", "answers": [ "まきはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "氷川", "answers": [ "ひかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "浜口", "answers": [ "はまぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大河原", "answers": [ "おおかわら", "おおがわら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "若本", "answers": [ "わかもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宗", "answers": [ "そう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "浅見", "answers": [ "あさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "戸川", "answers": [ "とがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "矢田", "answers": [ "やだ", "やた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "井川", "answers": [ "いがわ", "いかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "河原", "answers": [ "かわはら", "かわら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "元気", "answers": [ "げんき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "横井", "answers": [ "よこい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長谷部", "answers": [ "はせべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桜川", "answers": [ "おうかわ", "さくらがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "来生", "answers": [ "きすぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "杉村", "answers": [ "すぎむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "永吉", "answers": [ "ながよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "高城", "answers": [ "たかぎ", "たかじょう", "たかしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 25%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "小嶋", "answers": [ "こじま", "おじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "伊奈", "answers": [ "いな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%" },
	{ "question": "若山", "answers": [ "わかやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "藤川", "answers": [ "ふじかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "松嶋", "answers": [ "まつしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "坂東", "answers": [ "ばんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "竹山", "answers": [ "たけやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "礼", "answers": [ "れい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "新見", "answers": [ "にいみ", "しんみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "森口", "answers": [ "もりぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "堀口", "answers": [ "ほりぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "島本", "answers": [ "しまもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%" },
	{ "question": "董", "answers": [ "とう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "徐", "answers": [ "じょ", "ソ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "緒形", "answers": [ "おがた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "平沢", "answers": [ "ひらさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "金丸", "answers": [ "かねまる", "かなまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "飛鳥", "answers": [ "あすか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "宮島", "answers": [ "みやじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "瀬尾", "answers": [ "せお", "せのお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "守谷", "answers": [ "もりたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "安岡", "answers": [ "やすおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "緑", "answers": [ "みどり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 24%" },
	{ "question": "桑島", "answers": [ "くわしま", "くわじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "鴻巣", "answers": [ "こうのす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "柳家", "answers": [ "やなぎや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "塩沢", "answers": [ "しおざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "樹", "answers": [ "いつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "渥美", "answers": [ "あつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真子", "answers": [ "まご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "北斗", "answers": [ "ほくと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%" },
	{ "question": "塩谷", "answers": [ "しおのや", "しおや", "しおたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%, 21%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "九鬼", "answers": [ "くき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "有希", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "水沢", "answers": [ "みずさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "板東", "answers": [ "ばんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "梓", "answers": [ "あずさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "上戸", "answers": [ "うえと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "郷里", "answers": [ "ごうり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "菊田", "answers": [ "きくた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "北大路", "answers": [ "きたおおじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "輝", "answers": [ "らん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "前原", "answers": [ "まえはら", "まえばら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "千原", "answers": [ "ちはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小宮山", "answers": [ "こみやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "行田", "answers": [ "こうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "相原", "answers": [ "あいはら", "あいばら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "夏木", "answers": [ "なつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "春風亭", "answers": [ "しゅんぷうてい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "篠山", "answers": [ "しのやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "日置", "answers": [ "へき", "ひおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "依田", "answers": [ "よだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "高峰", "answers": [ "たかみね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "二本松", "answers": [ "にほんまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "長宗我部", "answers": [ "ちょうそかべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久世", "answers": [ "くぜ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "秦野", "answers": [ "はたの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "早坂", "answers": [ "はやさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "檀", "answers": [ "だん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "潮", "answers": [ "うしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%" },
	{ "question": "高砂", "answers": [ "たかさご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "寺内", "answers": [ "てらうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "里美", "answers": [ "さとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "財津", "answers": [ "ざいつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "荻原", "answers": [ "おぎわら", "おぎはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "池", "answers": [ "いけ", "いけの", "チ", "ジ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 15%, 11%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "千明", "answers": [ "ちぎら", "ちあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "平賀", "answers": [ "ひらが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "丹下", "answers": [ "たんげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田畑", "answers": [ "たばた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "竹原", "answers": [ "たけはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%" },
	{ "question": "加東", "answers": [ "かとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%" },
	{ "question": "水田", "answers": [ "みずた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "三枝", "answers": [ "さえぐさ", "さいぐさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "阪口", "answers": [ "さかぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奥井", "answers": [ "おくい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "西島", "answers": [ "にしじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "板野", "answers": [ "いたの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "船越", "answers": [ "ふなこし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "鳥山", "answers": [ "とりやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奥野", "answers": [ "おくの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "三波", "answers": [ "みなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "剣", "answers": [ "つるぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "萩本", "answers": [ "はぎもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芳賀", "answers": [ "はが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "野崎", "answers": [ "のざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "夏樹", "answers": [ "なつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%" },
	{ "question": "永山", "answers": [ "ながやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%" },
	{ "question": "鈴村", "answers": [ "すずむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "倉木", "answers": [ "くらき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "冬樹", "answers": [ "ふゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "赤塚", "answers": [ "あかつか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "富野", "answers": [ "とみの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "月亭", "answers": [ "つきてい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "井出", "answers": [ "いで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "高原", "answers": [ "たかはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "嶋", "answers": [ "しま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "天神", "answers": [ "てんじん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "築地", "answers": [ "つきじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "大東", "answers": [ "おおひがし", "だいとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 22%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "菅沼", "answers": [ "すがぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "白", "answers": [ "はく", "ペク" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "紺野", "answers": [ "こんの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "盧", "answers": [ "ノ", "ろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "喜多村", "answers": [ "きたむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宮地", "answers": [ "みやじ", "みやち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 33%" },
	{ "question": "大隈", "answers": [ "おおくま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "徳井", "answers": [ "とくい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "小清水", "answers": [ "こしみず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "秋本", "answers": [ "あきもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宗像", "answers": [ "むなかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "中丸", "answers": [ "なかまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "武井", "answers": [ "たけい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "姜", "answers": [ "カン", "きょう", "ジャン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 41%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "野呂", "answers": [ "のろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大伴", "answers": [ "おおとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "江田", "answers": [ "えだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "森繁", "answers": [ "もりしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高梁", "answers": [ "たかはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "桜庭", "answers": [ "さくらば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "春菜", "answers": [ "はるな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "瀬川", "answers": [ "せがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "阿蘇", "answers": [ "あそ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "花田", "answers": [ "はなだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "矢作", "answers": [ "やはぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "高森", "answers": [ "たかもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%" },
	{ "question": "船山", "answers": [ "ふなやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山城", "answers": [ "やましろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "川瀬", "answers": [ "かわせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "植松", "answers": [ "うえまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "磯部", "answers": [ "いそべ", "いそベ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "萩田", "answers": [ "はぎた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喬", "answers": [ "きょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "荒尾", "answers": [ "あらお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%" },
	{ "question": "小橋", "answers": [ "こばし", "こはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "安城", "answers": [ "あんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "山野", "answers": [ "やまの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "波多野", "answers": [ "はたの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浪川", "answers": [ "なみかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奥", "answers": [ "おく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鳳", "answers": [ "おおとり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%" },
	{ "question": "雨宮", "answers": [ "あめみや", "あまみや", "あめのみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 38%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "赤井", "answers": [ "あかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "高尾", "answers": [ "たかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%" },
	{ "question": "浅利", "answers": [ "あさり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "相生", "answers": [ "あいおい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "福留", "answers": [ "ふくとめ", "ふくどめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 43%" },
	{ "question": "護", "answers": [ "もり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "篠崎", "answers": [ "しのざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "深見", "answers": [ "ふかみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仲間", "answers": [ "なかま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "名護", "answers": [ "なご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "五條", "answers": [ "ごじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "倍賞", "answers": [ "ばいしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "城島", "answers": [ "じょうじま", "じょうしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 32%" },
	{ "question": "茜", "answers": [ "あかね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "沢城", "answers": [ "さわしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "尾形", "answers": [ "おがた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "忌野", "answers": [ "いまわの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "津村", "answers": [ "つむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "銀河", "answers": [ "ぎんが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "檜山", "answers": [ "ひやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "宇佐美", "answers": [ "うさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "千石", "answers": [ "せんごく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "亜希", "answers": [ "あき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "長州", "answers": [ "ちょうしゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "守口", "answers": [ "もりぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "鹿沼", "answers": [ "かぬま", "しかぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "陽", "answers": [ "よう", "ヤン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "梁", "answers": [ "りょう", "ヤン", "リャン", "やん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%, 12%, 8%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "長", "answers": [ "ちょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "三井", "answers": [ "みつい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "江崎", "answers": [ "えさき", "えざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "本宮", "answers": [ "もとみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%" },
	{ "question": "室井", "answers": [ "むろい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "志田", "answers": [ "しだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高柳", "answers": [ "たかやなぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "川澄", "answers": [ "かわすみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "樹里", "answers": [ "じゅり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "奥山", "answers": [ "おくやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "倉本", "answers": [ "くらもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "金本", "answers": [ "かねもと", "かなもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "岩佐", "answers": [ "いわさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "川井", "answers": [ "かわい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "柄本", "answers": [ "えもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "茅原", "answers": [ "ちはら", "かやはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "越智", "answers": [ "おち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長瀬", "answers": [ "ながせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "黒柳", "answers": [ "くろやなぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "巧", "answers": [ "たくみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "西沢", "answers": [ "にしざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "堀井", "answers": [ "ほりい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "九条", "answers": [ "くじょう", "きゅうじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "玉木", "answers": [ "たまき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "三石", "answers": [ "みついし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "中江", "answers": [ "なかえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝田", "answers": [ "かつた", "しょうだ", "かつだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 19%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "梅原", "answers": [ "うめはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "間宮", "answers": [ "まみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "泉谷", "answers": [ "いずみや", "いずたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "杏", "answers": [ "あんず", "あん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "進藤", "answers": [ "しんどう", "しんとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "今", "answers": [ "こん", "いま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "大澤", "answers": [ "おおさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "高嶋", "answers": [ "たかしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沖", "answers": [ "おき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "氷室", "answers": [ "ひむろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "宇喜多", "answers": [ "うきた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大手", "answers": [ "おおて" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "真木", "answers": [ "まき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "玉野", "answers": [ "たまの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "島谷", "answers": [ "しまたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "徳田", "answers": [ "とくだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "義家", "answers": [ "よしいえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "赤木", "answers": [ "あかぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "美馬", "answers": [ "みま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "笠間", "answers": [ "かさま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "秋野", "answers": [ "あきの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沢木", "answers": [ "さわき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "荻野目", "answers": [ "おぎのめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "八田", "answers": [ "はった", "やつだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "飛田", "answers": [ "とびた", "ひだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "坪内", "answers": [ "つぼうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "滑川", "answers": [ "なめかわ", "なめりかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "鴨川", "answers": [ "かもがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "出水", "answers": [ "でみず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%" },
	{ "question": "森脇", "answers": [ "もりわき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三ツ矢", "answers": [ "みつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "福地", "answers": [ "ふくち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "設楽", "answers": [ "したら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%" },
	{ "question": "宇崎", "answers": [ "うざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "森高", "answers": [ "もりたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "衛", "answers": [ "えい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "佐田", "answers": [ "さだ", "さた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "茂原", "answers": [ "しげはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "観月", "answers": [ "みづき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "燕", "answers": [ "えん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "長戸", "answers": [ "ながと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石松", "answers": [ "いしまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 22%" },
	{ "question": "山北", "answers": [ "やまきた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "米山", "answers": [ "よねやま", "こめやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "久野", "answers": [ "くの", "ひさの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "円", "answers": [ "まどか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%" },
	{ "question": "河田", "answers": [ "かわた", "かわだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%, 41%" },
	{ "question": "金城", "answers": [ "かねしろ", "きんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "黒岩", "answers": [ "くろいわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "金田一", "answers": [ "きんだいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "龍造寺", "answers": [ "りゅうぞうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "横尾", "answers": [ "よこお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "黛", "answers": [ "まゆずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小金井", "answers": [ "こがねい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "大門", "answers": [ "だいもん", "おおかど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "松川", "answers": [ "まつかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%" },
	{ "question": "滝", "answers": [ "たき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "白浜", "answers": [ "しらはま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "都築", "answers": [ "つづき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仙石", "answers": [ "せんごく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "柳井", "answers": [ "やない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "岩下", "answers": [ "いわした" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "安原", "answers": [ "やすはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "江夏", "answers": [ "えなつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "池谷", "answers": [ "いけたに", "いけや", "いけがや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%, 24%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "藤波", "answers": [ "ふじなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "大熊", "answers": [ "おおくま", "おぐま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "小畑", "answers": [ "おばた", "こばた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "佐山", "answers": [ "さやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "国", "answers": [ "こく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "梅宮", "answers": [ "うめみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "糸井", "answers": [ "いとい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "岳", "answers": [ "がく", "たけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "保科", "answers": [ "ほしな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "永瀬", "answers": [ "ながせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "彩乃", "answers": [ "あやの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "米田", "answers": [ "よねだ", "めた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "土肥", "answers": [ "どひ", "どい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 40%" },
	{ "question": "永", "answers": [ "えい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "長沢", "answers": [ "ながさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "出口", "answers": [ "でぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "芝", "answers": [ "しば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%" },
	{ "question": "石本", "answers": [ "いしもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浅香", "answers": [ "あさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "弥生", "answers": [ "やよい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "平原", "answers": [ "ひらはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "広川", "answers": [ "ひろかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%" },
	{ "question": "宮原", "answers": [ "みやはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "立原", "answers": [ "たちはら", "たつはら", "たてはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "石森", "answers": [ "いしもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "七海", "answers": [ "ななみ", "ななうみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "佐橋", "answers": [ "さはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉沢", "answers": [ "よしざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "大瀧", "answers": [ "おおたき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "横川", "answers": [ "よこかわ", "よこがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "臼井", "answers": [ "うすい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "滝口", "answers": [ "たきぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "阿川", "answers": [ "あがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "岡谷", "answers": [ "おかや", "おかたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "水橋", "answers": [ "みずはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "桜木", "answers": [ "さくらぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%" },
	{ "question": "栗本", "answers": [ "くりもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "大浦", "answers": [ "おおうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "赤星", "answers": [ "あかほし", "あかぼし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "辰野", "answers": [ "たつの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%" },
	{ "question": "竹島", "answers": [ "たけしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "重松", "answers": [ "しげまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "沢口", "answers": [ "さわぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浜村", "answers": [ "はまむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "岸部", "answers": [ "きしべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "阪本", "answers": [ "さかもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "江", "answers": [ "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "岩瀬", "answers": [ "いわせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "宇垣", "answers": [ "うがき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和", "answers": [ "かず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "真野", "answers": [ "まの", "まや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 26%" },
	{ "question": "松木", "answers": [ "まつき", "まつのき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "徳山", "answers": [ "とくやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "佐川", "answers": [ "さがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%" },
	{ "question": "山鹿", "answers": [ "やまが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%" },
	{ "question": "角川", "answers": [ "かどかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "持田", "answers": [ "もちだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "細田", "answers": [ "ほそだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "藤野", "answers": [ "ふじの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "広末", "answers": [ "ひろすえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "戸沢", "answers": [ "とざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "田", "answers": [ "でん", "ティエン", "チョン", "ヒビ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 5%, 3%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "天海", "answers": [ "あまみ", "てんかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "三橋", "answers": [ "みつはし", "みはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 43%" },
	{ "question": "前野", "answers": [ "まえの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "潘", "answers": [ "はん", "パン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "長沼", "answers": [ "ながぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%" },
	{ "question": "壬生", "answers": [ "みぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%" },
	{ "question": "田沼", "answers": [ "たぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "龍田", "answers": [ "たつた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "菅井", "answers": [ "すがい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "甲斐田", "answers": [ "かいだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "宮部", "answers": [ "みやべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "水森", "answers": [ "みずもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "葛城", "answers": [ "かつらぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "深浦", "answers": [ "ふかうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%" },
	{ "question": "井手", "answers": [ "いで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "備前", "answers": [ "びぜん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "出川", "answers": [ "でがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "野原", "answers": [ "のはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久本", "answers": [ "ひさもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "若菜", "answers": [ "わかな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%" },
	{ "question": "真矢", "answers": [ "まや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "小津", "answers": [ "おづ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "青柳", "answers": [ "あおやぎ", "あおやなぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "相澤", "answers": [ "あいざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "橋", "answers": [ "はし", "きょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "富永", "answers": [ "とみなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "杜", "answers": [ "と", "もり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "塚原", "answers": [ "つかはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "杏子", "answers": [ "あんず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "屋良", "answers": [ "やら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "間", "answers": [ "はざま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大蔵", "answers": [ "おおくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%" },
	{ "question": "天童", "answers": [ "てんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "東国原", "answers": [ "ひがしこくばる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "岩村", "answers": [ "いわむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "須賀", "answers": [ "すが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "今西", "answers": [ "いまにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "犬養", "answers": [ "いぬかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "真島", "answers": [ "ましま", "まじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 27%" },
	{ "question": "美月", "answers": [ "みつき", "みづき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "広田", "answers": [ "ひろた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "浜", "answers": [ "はま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "河原崎", "answers": [ "かわらさき", "かわらざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "荻野", "answers": [ "おぎの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "坂戸", "answers": [ "さかと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "小国", "answers": [ "おぐに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "三池", "answers": [ "みいけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小日向", "answers": [ "こひなた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "木津川", "answers": [ "きづがわ", "きつかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "臼杵", "answers": [ "うすき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "澤", "answers": [ "さわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小堀", "answers": [ "こぼり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宇城", "answers": [ "うしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "田宮", "answers": [ "たみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "柴咲", "answers": [ "しばさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竹村", "answers": [ "たけむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "森村", "answers": [ "もりむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "長山", "answers": [ "ながやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "鹿内", "answers": [ "しかない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恩田", "answers": [ "おんだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "小椋", "answers": [ "おぐら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "権", "answers": [ "クォン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "高梨", "answers": [ "たかなし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "佳織", "answers": [ "かおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "柚木", "answers": [ "ゆずき", "ゆき", "ゆのき", "ゆぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 11%, 6%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "土居", "answers": [ "どい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "澤田", "answers": [ "さわだ", "さわた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "与謝野", "answers": [ "よさの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%" },
	{ "question": "久川", "answers": [ "ひさかわ", "くがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "木原", "answers": [ "きはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "優希", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%" },
	{ "question": "並木", "answers": [ "なみき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "大空", "answers": [ "おおぞら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "隼", "answers": [ "はやぶさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "清瀬", "answers": [ "きよせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "安中", "answers": [ "あんなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "直江", "answers": [ "なおえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "天龍", "answers": [ "てんりゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "千住", "answers": [ "せんじゅ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%" },
	{ "question": "匠", "answers": [ "たくみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "山県", "answers": [ "やまがた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%" },
	{ "question": "若槻", "answers": [ "わかつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宮野", "answers": [ "みやの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "上松", "answers": [ "あげまつ", "うえまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "島原", "answers": [ "しまばら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "大前", "answers": [ "おおまえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "佐渡島", "answers": [ "さどしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "田山", "answers": [ "たやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "河井", "answers": [ "かわい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "日吉", "answers": [ "ひよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%" },
	{ "question": "尾鷲", "answers": [ "おわし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "本居", "answers": [ "もとおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "猪苗代", "answers": [ "いなわしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "根津", "answers": [ "ねづ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "東海林", "answers": [ "しょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "許", "answers": [ "きょ", "ホ", "シュウ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 19%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "鹿野", "answers": [ "かの", "しかの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "吉澤", "answers": [ "よしざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "嘉門", "answers": [ "かもん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "市村", "answers": [ "いちむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "黒石", "answers": [ "くろいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "相田", "answers": [ "あいだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "勝生", "answers": [ "かつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "垂水", "answers": [ "たるみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%" },
	{ "question": "正岡", "answers": [ "まさおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高須", "answers": [ "たかす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "日下", "answers": [ "くさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "船木", "answers": [ "ふなき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "蒼井", "answers": [ "あおい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三田村", "answers": [ "みたむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "堀越", "answers": [ "ほりこし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "藤間", "answers": [ "ふじま", "とうま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "高畠", "answers": [ "たかばたけ", "たかはた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "薬師丸", "answers": [ "やくしまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "廣田", "answers": [ "ひろた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富沢", "answers": [ "とみざわ", "とみさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "木戸", "answers": [ "きど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "海部", "answers": [ "かいふ", "かいべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "井筒", "answers": [ "いづつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朝比奈", "answers": [ "あさひな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "堀部", "answers": [ "ほりべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "日笠", "answers": [ "ひかさ", "ひがさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "錦織", "answers": [ "にしきおり", "にしこり", "にしこおり", "にしごり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%, 28%, 12%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "富樫", "answers": [ "とがし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "磯野", "answers": [ "いその" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "永島", "answers": [ "ながしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田尻", "answers": [ "たじり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "広岡", "answers": [ "ひろおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "乃木", "answers": [ "のぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "西谷", "answers": [ "にしたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "豊崎", "answers": [ "とよさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "浦上", "answers": [ "うらがみ", "うらかみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%, 33%" },
	{ "question": "蒲田", "answers": [ "がまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "赤穂", "answers": [ "あかほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "濱口", "answers": [ "はまぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "丁", "answers": [ "てい", "チョン", "ジョン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 11%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "朝青龍", "answers": [ "あさしょうりゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "火野", "answers": [ "ひの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中里", "answers": [ "なかざと", "なかさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "寺山", "answers": [ "てらやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "城山", "answers": [ "しろやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "島村", "answers": [ "しまむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真実", "answers": [ "しんじつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "岩沼", "answers": [ "いわぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "島香", "answers": [ "しまか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "本木", "answers": [ "もとき", "もとぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "境", "answers": [ "さかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%" },
	{ "question": "石毛", "answers": [ "いしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蔡", "answers": [ "さい", "チェ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "丘", "answers": [ "おか", "きゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "高千穂", "answers": [ "たかちほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "藤吉", "answers": [ "ふじよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%" },
	{ "question": "田端", "answers": [ "たばた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%" },
	{ "question": "金光", "answers": [ "かねみつ", "かなみつ", "こんこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 31%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "指宿", "answers": [ "いぶすき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "英", "answers": [ "はなぶさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%" },
	{ "question": "古今亭", "answers": [ "ここんてい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "門脇", "answers": [ "かどわき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大下", "answers": [ "おおした", "おおしも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "眞", "answers": [ "さな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "仲谷", "answers": [ "なかや", "なかたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "木田", "answers": [ "きだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "岩松", "answers": [ "いわまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "犬塚", "answers": [ "いぬづか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "宇文", "answers": [ "うぶん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和気", "answers": [ "わけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%" },
	{ "question": "宝亀", "answers": [ "ほうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "冨永", "answers": [ "とみなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "代々木", "answers": [ "よよぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "保田", "answers": [ "やすだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "保志", "answers": [ "ほし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "田淵", "answers": [ "たぶち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "川嶋", "answers": [ "かわしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "押井", "answers": [ "おしい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "安東", "answers": [ "あんどう", "あんとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "安来", "answers": [ "あんらい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "北本", "answers": [ "きたもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%" },
	{ "question": "村瀬", "answers": [ "むらせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "辺見", "answers": [ "へんみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "藤谷", "answers": [ "ふじたに", "ふじや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "林田", "answers": [ "はやしだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "笹川", "answers": [ "ささかわ", "ささがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "曽我部", "answers": [ "そがべ", "そかべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 46%" },
	{ "question": "下條", "answers": [ "しもじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "京田", "answers": [ "きょうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "志麻", "answers": [ "しま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "美川", "answers": [ "みかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "近田", "answers": [ "ちかだ", "こんだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "立山", "answers": [ "たてやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "土橋", "answers": [ "どばし", "つちはし", "つちばし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 21%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "夏侯", "answers": [ "かこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高石", "answers": [ "たかいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "海津", "answers": [ "かいづ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "冬馬", "answers": [ "とうま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "町村", "answers": [ "まちむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "魯", "answers": [ "ろ", "ノ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "翠", "answers": [ "みどり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "邦", "answers": [ "くに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "本", "answers": [ "もと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "仲野", "answers": [ "なかの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有本", "answers": [ "ありもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "唐", "answers": [ "とう", "から", "タン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 43%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "増山", "answers": [ "ますやま", "ましやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 32%" },
	{ "question": "古屋", "answers": [ "ふるや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "天田", "answers": [ "あまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "増岡", "answers": [ "ますおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "古澤", "answers": [ "ふるさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊福部", "answers": [ "いふくべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "男鹿", "answers": [ "おが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "長谷", "answers": [ "はせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "田丸", "answers": [ "たまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "深水", "answers": [ "しんすい", "ふかみ", "ふかみず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%, 27%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "藤島", "answers": [ "ふじしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "橋田", "answers": [ "はしだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秋月", "answers": [ "あきづき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "華", "answers": [ "か", "はな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "白木", "answers": [ "しらき", "しろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "諏訪部", "answers": [ "すわべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "水前寺", "answers": [ "すいぜんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "衛藤", "answers": [ "えとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夏生", "answers": [ "なつお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "玄", "answers": [ "ヒョン", "げん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "貴乃花", "answers": [ "たかのはな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高倉", "answers": [ "たかくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "岩永", "answers": [ "いわなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大中", "answers": [ "おおなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "伏見", "answers": [ "ふしみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "團", "answers": [ "だん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "坂", "answers": [ "さか", "ばん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "石山", "answers": [ "いしやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "壮", "answers": [ "そう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "古舘", "answers": [ "ふるたち", "ふるだて" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "玉井", "answers": [ "たまい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝部", "answers": [ "かつべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "守屋", "answers": [ "もりや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%" },
	{ "question": "阪田", "answers": [ "さかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "川野", "answers": [ "かわの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "嵐山", "answers": [ "あらしやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%" },
	{ "question": "名和", "answers": [ "なわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "上岡", "answers": [ "かみおか", "うえおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "武士", "answers": [ "たけし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "座間", "answers": [ "ざま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "糸島", "answers": [ "いとじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "深沢", "answers": [ "ふかさわ", "ふかざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 34%" },
	{ "question": "今泉", "answers": [ "いまいずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "押上", "answers": [ "おうかみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "諸星", "answers": [ "もろほし", "もろぼし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "高見沢", "answers": [ "たかみざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "古市", "answers": [ "ふるいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%" },
	{ "question": "柴", "answers": [ "しば", "さい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "河上", "answers": [ "かわかみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小木", "answers": [ "おぎ", "こぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "梶山", "answers": [ "かじやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大矢", "answers": [ "おおや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "岩尾", "answers": [ "いわお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有村", "answers": [ "ありむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "八奈見", "answers": [ "やなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "野間", "answers": [ "のま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "土佐", "answers": [ "とさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%" },
	{ "question": "一戸", "answers": [ "いちのへ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%" },
	{ "question": "宮村", "answers": [ "みやむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "正木", "answers": [ "まさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "笹野", "answers": [ "ささの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久石", "answers": [ "ひさいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "花澤", "answers": [ "はなざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "滝田", "answers": [ "たきた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重光", "answers": [ "しげみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "生天目", "answers": [ "なばため" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "愛菜", "answers": [ "あいな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 36%" },
	{ "question": "谷本", "answers": [ "たにもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "横溝", "answers": [ "よこみぞ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "睦", "answers": [ "むつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%" },
	{ "question": "城戸", "answers": [ "きど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "笠松", "answers": [ "かさまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "飯山", "answers": [ "いいやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "笠", "answers": [ "りゅう", "かさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "森谷", "answers": [ "もりや", "もりたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%, 50%" },
	{ "question": "紫", "answers": [ "むらさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "比嘉", "answers": [ "ひが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "中根", "answers": [ "なかね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "棚橋", "answers": [ "たなはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喜多", "answers": [ "きた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "蕨", "answers": [ "わらび" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "小堺", "answers": [ "こさかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "魏", "answers": [ "ぎ", "ギ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "阿木", "answers": [ "あき", "あぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "熊田", "answers": [ "くまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "草刈", "answers": [ "くさかり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "有楽", "answers": [ "うらく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "野茂", "answers": [ "のも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "南條", "answers": [ "なんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "江本", "answers": [ "えもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "磯村", "answers": [ "いそむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有賀", "answers": [ "ありが", "あるが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 36%" },
	{ "question": "大柴", "answers": [ "おおしば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "鷲尾", "answers": [ "わしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "草尾", "answers": [ "くさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "金村", "answers": [ "かねむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "謝", "answers": [ "しゃ", "シェイ", "しぇい", "シエ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%, 32%, 11%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "定岡", "answers": [ "さだおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "曙", "answers": [ "あけぼの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "万里", "answers": [ "ばんり", "まり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "美濃", "answers": [ "みの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "崎谷", "answers": [ "さきや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "矢崎", "answers": [ "やざき", "やさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "武満", "answers": [ "たけみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "藤懸", "answers": [ "ふじかけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "関本", "answers": [ "せきもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大吉", "answers": [ "おおよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "都留", "answers": [ "つる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%" },
	{ "question": "馮", "answers": [ "ふう", "ひょう", "フォン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 8%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "戸松", "answers": [ "とまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鶴", "answers": [ "つる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "美波", "answers": [ "みなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "清須", "answers": [ "きよす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "柳澤", "answers": [ "やなぎさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "萩尾", "answers": [ "はぎお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "辻村", "answers": [ "つじむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "金原", "answers": [ "かねはら", "きんばら", "かなはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 30%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "香椎", "answers": [ "かしい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%" },
	{ "question": "眞鍋", "answers": [ "まなべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "豊口", "answers": [ "とよぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "下妻", "answers": [ "しもづま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "小幡", "answers": [ "おばた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "汪", "answers": [ "おう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "安彦", "answers": [ "やすひこ", "あびこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "村川", "answers": [ "むらかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊武", "answers": [ "いぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夏海", "answers": [ "なつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "新島", "answers": [ "にいじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%" },
	{ "question": "天地", "answers": [ "あまち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "津軽", "answers": [ "つがる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高垣", "answers": [ "たかがき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "坂下", "answers": [ "さかした" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "生島", "answers": [ "いくしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "行方", "answers": [ "なめかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "西崎", "answers": [ "にしざき", "にしさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "田坂", "answers": [ "たさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "片平", "answers": [ "かたひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "何", "answers": [ "か", "が" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "脇坂", "answers": [ "わきさか", "わきざか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "赤城", "answers": [ "あかぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "蛯名", "answers": [ "えびな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝山", "answers": [ "かつやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "白鵬", "answers": [ "はくほう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "神楽坂", "answers": [ "かぐらざか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%" },
	{ "question": "山瀬", "answers": [ "やませ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "山里", "answers": [ "やまさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "柴崎", "answers": [ "しばさき", "しばざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "国生", "answers": [ "こくしょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "岩谷", "answers": [ "いわたに", "いわや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "中岡", "answers": [ "なかおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "氏家", "answers": [ "うじいえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "養父", "answers": [ "やぶ", "ようふ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "守山", "answers": [ "もりやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "反町", "answers": [ "そりまち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "和光", "answers": [ "わこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "夏", "answers": [ "なつ", "か", "シャー", "シア" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 12%, 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "甲本", "answers": [ "こうもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石崎", "answers": [ "いしざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "両国", "answers": [ "りょうごく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "石狩", "answers": [ "いしかり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "松林", "answers": [ "まつばやし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "鮫島", "answers": [ "さめしま", "さめじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 37%" },
	{ "question": "木暮", "answers": [ "こぐれ", "きぐれ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "京本", "answers": [ "きょうもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "八神", "answers": [ "やがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "舘", "answers": [ "たち", "たて" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "深津", "answers": [ "ふかつ", "ふかづ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "波田", "answers": [ "はた", "はだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "下山", "answers": [ "しもやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "西條", "answers": [ "さいじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三平", "answers": [ "みひら", "みつひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "坂元", "answers": [ "さかもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "阪", "answers": [ "さか", "ばん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "水城", "answers": [ "みずき", "みずしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "団", "answers": [ "だん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "岸尾", "answers": [ "きしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "牛島", "answers": [ "うしじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "環", "answers": [ "たまき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "蓮田", "answers": [ "はすだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "高萩", "answers": [ "たかはぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "山室", "answers": [ "やまむろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "江角", "answers": [ "えすみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "園部", "answers": [ "そのべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%" },
	{ "question": "楓", "answers": [ "かえで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%" },
	{ "question": "若葉", "answers": [ "わかば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%" },
	{ "question": "森久保", "answers": [ "もりくぼ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "東尾", "answers": [ "ひがしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "草薙", "answers": [ "くさなぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "長嶋", "answers": [ "ながしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "売野", "answers": [ "うりの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梁田", "answers": [ "やなだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "太地", "answers": [ "たいじ", "たいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "多賀", "answers": [ "たが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%" },
	{ "question": "紅", "answers": [ "くれない", "こう", "あかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%, 23%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "保坂", "answers": [ "ほさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大庭", "answers": [ "おおば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "住吉", "answers": [ "すみよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%" },
	{ "question": "芹沢", "answers": [ "せりざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "木根", "answers": [ "きね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻耶", "answers": [ "まや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "覚", "answers": [ "かく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "匡", "answers": [ "きょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "南城", "answers": [ "なんじょう", "みなしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "山元", "answers": [ "やまもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%" },
	{ "question": "村野", "answers": [ "むらの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "塩見", "answers": [ "しおみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勝俣", "answers": [ "かつまた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清治", "answers": [ "せいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "添田", "answers": [ "そえだ", "そえた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 44%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "洪", "answers": [ "ホン", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "峰岸", "answers": [ "みねぎし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "布川", "answers": [ "ふかわ", "ぬのかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "川俣", "answers": [ "かわまた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%" },
	{ "question": "稲森", "answers": [ "いなもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "妹尾", "answers": [ "せのお", "せお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "芝山", "answers": [ "しばやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%" },
	{ "question": "伊原", "answers": [ "いはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "三善", "answers": [ "みよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宮武", "answers": [ "みやたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "萬屋", "answers": [ "よろずや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宮迫", "answers": [ "みやさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松谷", "answers": [ "まつたに", "まつや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "広橋", "answers": [ "ひろはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "橋口", "answers": [ "はしぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "木谷", "answers": [ "きたに", "きだに", "こたに", "きや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 22%, 4%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "湖西", "answers": [ "こにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "野上", "answers": [ "のがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "真鍋", "answers": [ "まなべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "平岩", "answers": [ "ひらいわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "泉水", "answers": [ "せんすい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "寒川", "answers": [ "さむかわ", "さんがわ", "かんがわ", "さがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%, 7%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "愛内", "answers": [ "あいうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "若狭", "answers": [ "わかさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 32%" },
	{ "question": "千", "answers": [ "せん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "関川", "answers": [ "せきかわ", "せきがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 44%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "岸野", "answers": [ "きしの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "黒須", "answers": [ "くろす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "樹木", "answers": [ "きき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "池波", "answers": [ "いけなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恵比寿", "answers": [ "えびす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "安川", "answers": [ "やすかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "藤林", "answers": [ "ふじばやし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "近衛", "answers": [ "このえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "樋浦", "answers": [ "ひうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "安芸", "answers": [ "あき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "少弐", "answers": [ "しょうに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "郷田", "answers": [ "ごうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "河津", "answers": [ "かわづ", "かわつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "湊", "answers": [ "みなと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%" },
	{ "question": "羽佐間", "answers": [ "はざま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "名塚", "answers": [ "なづか", "なつか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "佐古", "answers": [ "さこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%" },
	{ "question": "華原", "answers": [ "かはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "筧", "answers": [ "かけい", "かけひ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "小野坂", "answers": [ "おのさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "内野", "answers": [ "うちの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "井田", "answers": [ "いだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "那珂", "answers": [ "なか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "辛島", "answers": [ "からしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "笠井", "answers": [ "かさい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "能勢", "answers": [ "のせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%" },
	{ "question": "吉", "answers": [ "よし", "きつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "鈴置", "answers": [ "すずおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小峰", "answers": [ "こみね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松陰", "answers": [ "まつかげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "亜樹", "answers": [ "あき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 32%" },
	{ "question": "下松", "answers": [ "しもまつ", "くだまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "野々村", "answers": [ "ののむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高階", "answers": [ "たかしな", "たかしなの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "篠塚", "answers": [ "しのづか", "しのつか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "磯崎", "answers": [ "いそざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "哀川", "answers": [ "あいかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "福士", "answers": [ "ふくし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一青", "answers": [ "ひとと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "加地", "answers": [ "かじ", "かぢ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 40%" },
	{ "question": "畑中", "answers": [ "はたなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "生瀬", "answers": [ "なませ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "川北", "answers": [ "かわきた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%" },
	{ "question": "仲", "answers": [ "なか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "月形", "answers": [ "つきがた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%" },
	{ "question": "陶", "answers": [ "すえ", "とう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%, 48%" },
	{ "question": "村岡", "answers": [ "むらおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "温水", "answers": [ "ぬくみず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "仲代", "answers": [ "なかだい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小寺", "answers": [ "こでら", "こてら", "おでら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%, 23%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "木梨", "answers": [ "きなし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "谷原", "answers": [ "たにはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "菅生", "answers": [ "すごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "新村", "answers": [ "しんむら", "にいむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "亘理", "answers": [ "わたり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "阿久根", "answers": [ "あくね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "尾上", "answers": [ "おのうえ", "おのえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 46%" },
	{ "question": "真樹", "answers": [ "まき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "北方", "answers": [ "きたかた", "きたがた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "塙", "answers": [ "はなわ", "ばん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "都倉", "answers": [ "とくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "塩野", "answers": [ "しおの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長坂", "answers": [ "ながさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "稲村", "answers": [ "いなむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "稲尾", "answers": [ "いなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "池澤", "answers": [ "いけざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雅", "answers": [ "みやび", "みや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "大磯", "answers": [ "おおいそ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "本橋", "answers": [ "もとはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蟹江", "answers": [ "かにえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%" },
	{ "question": "有森", "answers": [ "ありもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重盛", "answers": [ "しげもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%" },
	{ "question": "雪野", "answers": [ "ゆきの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "浅沼", "answers": [ "あさぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "細谷", "answers": [ "ほそや", "ほそたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "高取", "answers": [ "たかとり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%" },
	{ "question": "東根", "answers": [ "ひがしね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "松来", "answers": [ "まつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "廣瀬", "answers": [ "ひろせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "十朱", "answers": [ "とあけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久光", "answers": [ "ひさみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "堂島", "answers": [ "どうじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%" },
	{ "question": "由良", "answers": [ "ゆら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%" },
	{ "question": "二又", "answers": [ "ふたまた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "瀧本", "answers": [ "たきもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秀平", "answers": [ "ひでひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "十津川", "answers": [ "とつがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "氷上", "answers": [ "ひかみ", "ひがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "関谷", "answers": [ "せきや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大滝", "answers": [ "おおたき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "将司", "answers": [ "まさつかさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "梢", "answers": [ "こずえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "広尾", "answers": [ "ひろお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "堀北", "answers": [ "ほりきた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "海野", "answers": [ "うんの", "うみの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "彩夏", "answers": [ "さいか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "深井", "answers": [ "ふかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "新津", "answers": [ "にいつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%" },
	{ "question": "南国", "answers": [ "みなぐに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "大口", "answers": [ "おおぐち", "おおくち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "余", "answers": [ "よ", "ヨ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "阿澄", "answers": [ "あすみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "苅田", "answers": [ "かりた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "荘", "answers": [ "チュアン", "しょう", "そう", "ジュアン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%, 33%, 18%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "手島", "answers": [ "てじま", "てしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%, 48%" },
	{ "question": "神代", "answers": [ "こうじろ", "くましろ", "かみしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%, 37%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "岩男", "answers": [ "いわお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "青田", "answers": [ "あおた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "真殿", "answers": [ "まどの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "香坂", "answers": [ "こうさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "益子", "answers": [ "ますこ", "ましこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 24%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "小桜", "answers": [ "こざくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松元", "answers": [ "まつもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "西澤", "answers": [ "にしざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高樹", "answers": [ "たかぎ", "たかき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 30%" },
	{ "question": "春奈", "answers": [ "はるな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "槇", "answers": [ "まき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "浦沢", "answers": [ "うらさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宮口", "answers": [ "みやぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "中上", "answers": [ "なかがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "生野", "answers": [ "しょうの", "いくの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "串田", "answers": [ "くしだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "勇気", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "近江", "answers": [ "おうみ", "おおみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "元町", "answers": [ "もとまち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "佐佐木", "answers": [ "ささき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "温", "answers": [ "おん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%" },
	{ "question": "久弥", "answers": [ "ひさや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "一馬", "answers": [ "かずま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "砂川", "answers": [ "すながわ", "すなかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "宮尾", "answers": [ "みやお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "不破", "answers": [ "ふわ", "ふは" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "戸部", "answers": [ "とべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "須永", "answers": [ "すなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石破", "answers": [ "いしば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "庵野", "answers": [ "あんの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴司", "answers": [ "きし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "彩花", "answers": [ "あやか", "あやはな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "轟", "answers": [ "とどろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "寺本", "answers": [ "てらもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "寺岡", "answers": [ "てらおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鷺巣", "answers": [ "さぎす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "國府田", "answers": [ "こうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊沢", "answers": [ "いざわ", "いさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "芦川", "answers": [ "あしかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "角", "answers": [ "すみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "河西", "answers": [ "かさい", "かわにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "士郎", "answers": [ "しろう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%" },
	{ "question": "美濃部", "answers": [ "みのべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "日比野", "answers": [ "ひびの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "逢坂", "answers": [ "おうさか", "おおさか", "あいさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 10%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "赤川", "answers": [ "あかがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "有明", "answers": [ "ありあけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "山谷", "answers": [ "やまや", "やまたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 34%" },
	{ "question": "森崎", "answers": [ "もりさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "里田", "answers": [ "さとだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "珠洲", "answers": [ "すず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "松居", "answers": [ "まつい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "平林", "answers": [ "ひらばやし", "ひらはやし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "二条", "answers": [ "にじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "勝野", "answers": [ "かつの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "心", "answers": [ "こころ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "家中", "answers": [ "やなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "矢尾", "answers": [ "やお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "箕輪", "answers": [ "みのわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "種田", "answers": [ "たねだ", "おいた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "宇土", "answers": [ "うと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "吉崎", "answers": [ "よしざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "柳葉", "answers": [ "やなぎば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "袴田", "answers": [ "はかまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夏八木", "answers": [ "なつやぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高宮", "answers": [ "たかみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "瀬名", "answers": [ "せな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広野", "answers": [ "ひろの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "米村", "answers": [ "よねむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富川", "answers": [ "とみかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 44%" },
	{ "question": "宮藤", "answers": [ "くどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "川尻", "answers": [ "かわじり", "かわしり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "板尾", "answers": [ "いたお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "池江", "answers": [ "いけえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "綾乃", "answers": [ "あやの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "一葉", "answers": [ "いちよう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "小城", "answers": [ "おぎ", "こしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "風見", "answers": [ "かざみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "秋吉", "answers": [ "あきよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "達", "answers": [ "たつ", "たち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "早瀬", "answers": [ "はやせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "魚住", "answers": [ "うおずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "明乃", "answers": [ "あかりの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "山上", "answers": [ "やまがみ", "やまのうえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 27%" },
	{ "question": "草川", "answers": [ "くさかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "門田", "answers": [ "かどた", "もんでん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "富士川", "answers": [ "ふじかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "乃村", "answers": [ "のむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "二木", "answers": [ "にき", "ふたき", "ふたつき", "ふたつぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%, 32%, 17%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "雫石", "answers": [ "しずくいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "塩崎", "answers": [ "しおざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "高坂", "answers": [ "こうさか", "たかさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "熊倉", "answers": [ "くまくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小野田", "answers": [ "おのだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%" },
	{ "question": "大仁田", "answers": [ "おおにた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "江幡", "answers": [ "えばた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "匝瑳", "answers": [ "そうさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "北浜", "answers": [ "きたはま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%" },
	{ "question": "竹井", "answers": [ "たけい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "川辺", "answers": [ "かわべ", "かわなべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "朱音", "answers": [ "あかね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "頼", "answers": [ "らい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "神奈", "answers": [ "かんな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "角松", "answers": [ "かどまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "安奈", "answers": [ "あんな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%" },
	{ "question": "吉行", "answers": [ "よしゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "谷垣", "answers": [ "たにがき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田岡", "answers": [ "たおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "柿崎", "answers": [ "かきざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%" },
	{ "question": "稲川", "answers": [ "いながわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "新山", "answers": [ "にいやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小久保", "answers": [ "こくぼ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大高", "answers": [ "おおたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "大坂", "answers": [ "おおさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "吉松", "answers": [ "よしまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%" },
	{ "question": "真山", "answers": [ "まやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鳥越", "answers": [ "とりごえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "財前", "answers": [ "ざいぜん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "片瀬", "answers": [ "かたせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "伊織", "answers": [ "いおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "彭", "answers": [ "ポン", "ほう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "星川", "answers": [ "ほしかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "尾藤", "answers": [ "びとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "曽根", "answers": [ "そね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "川津", "answers": [ "かわづ", "かわつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "元信", "answers": [ "もとのぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "役所", "answers": [ "やくしょ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "橋爪", "answers": [ "はしづめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "土師", "answers": [ "はし", "はじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "住田", "answers": [ "すみだ", "すみた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "若草", "answers": [ "わかくさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "森次", "answers": [ "もりつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長嶝", "answers": [ "ながさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蝶野", "answers": [ "ちょうの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沈", "answers": [ "しん", "シム", "ちん", "シェン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 9%, 4%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "塩田", "answers": [ "しおた", "しおだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "宇田", "answers": [ "うだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美唄", "answers": [ "びばい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "向田", "answers": [ "むこうだ", "むかいだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 26%" },
	{ "question": "津嘉山", "answers": [ "つかやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "段", "answers": [ "だん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "大賀", "answers": [ "おおが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和希", "answers": [ "かずき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%" },
	{ "question": "三ノ宮", "answers": [ "さんのみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "九重", "answers": [ "ここのえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%" },
	{ "question": "三國", "answers": [ "みくに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中本", "answers": [ "なかもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "菅田", "answers": [ "すがた", "すだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "斎賀", "answers": [ "さいが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "赤西", "answers": [ "あかにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "双葉", "answers": [ "ふたば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%" },
	{ "question": "大鵬", "answers": [ "たいほう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "高岩", "answers": [ "たかいわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "猪俣", "answers": [ "いのまた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "水嶋", "answers": [ "みずしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千種", "answers": [ "ちぐさ", "ちくさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 24%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "多岐川", "answers": [ "たきがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蛭子", "answers": [ "えびす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "基", "answers": [ "もとい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "徳", "answers": [ "とく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "筑紫", "answers": [ "ちくし", "つくし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "俵", "answers": [ "たわら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "合田", "answers": [ "ごうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朝香", "answers": [ "あさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "千野", "answers": [ "ちの", "せんの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "柿原", "answers": [ "かきはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉彦", "answers": [ "きみこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "盛", "answers": [ "もり", "せい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "千代の富士", "answers": [ "ちよのふじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "副島", "answers": [ "そえじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大畑", "answers": [ "おおはた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "三戸", "answers": [ "みと", "さんのへ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 32%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "神野", "answers": [ "じんの", "しんの", "かみの", "かんの", "こうの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%, 27%, 20%, 4%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "倉橋", "answers": [ "くらはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "朽木", "answers": [ "くつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "片倉", "answers": [ "かたくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "廉", "answers": [ "ヨム", "れん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "末広", "answers": [ "すえひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "小菅", "answers": [ "こすげ", "こすが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "祇園", "answers": [ "ぎおん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "笹本", "answers": [ "ささもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幹", "answers": [ "みき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "羽衣", "answers": [ "はごろも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "五十鈴", "answers": [ "いすず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "美輪", "answers": [ "みわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "芹澤", "answers": [ "せりざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "四位", "answers": [ "しい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "金谷", "answers": [ "かなや", "かなたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "大城", "answers": [ "おおしろ", "おおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "野辺地", "answers": [ "のべち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "根谷", "answers": [ "ねや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "樺山", "answers": [ "かばやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "近松", "answers": [ "ちかまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "須崎", "answers": [ "すさき", "すざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "薬丸", "answers": [ "やくまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浦賀", "answers": [ "うらが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "藤江", "answers": [ "ふじえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "友", "answers": [ "とも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "中間", "answers": [ "なかま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "優木", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "山西", "answers": [ "やまにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "班", "answers": [ "はん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "瀬奈", "answers": [ "せな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "小関", "answers": [ "こせき", "おぜき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "公孫", "answers": [ "こうそん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "南条", "answers": [ "なんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "高久", "answers": [ "たかく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%" },
	{ "question": "草笛", "answers": [ "くさぶえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "押川", "answers": [ "おしかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊能", "answers": [ "いのう", "イノウ", "いよく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 7%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "真壁", "answers": [ "まかべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "齊藤", "answers": [ "さいとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "超", "answers": [ "チャオ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "羽村", "answers": [ "はむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "杉戸", "answers": [ "すぎと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "桂川", "answers": [ "かつらがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 24%" },
	{ "question": "知念", "answers": [ "ちねん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佐原", "answers": [ "さはら", "さわら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "北の湖", "answers": [ "きたのうみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "上條", "answers": [ "かみじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "賈", "answers": [ "か", "ジャ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "岬", "answers": [ "みさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 27%" },
	{ "question": "水口", "answers": [ "みずぐち", "みなくち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "鳴海", "answers": [ "なるみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%" },
	{ "question": "島袋", "answers": [ "しまぶくろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "江守", "answers": [ "えもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "横内", "answers": [ "よこうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "丸谷", "answers": [ "まるや", "まるたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "具志堅", "answers": [ "ぐしけん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大沼", "answers": [ "おおぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "宮", "answers": [ "みや", "ぐう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "歌川", "answers": [ "うたがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "于", "answers": [ "う" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山野井", "answers": [ "やまのい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浜中", "answers": [ "はまなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%" },
	{ "question": "玉田", "answers": [ "たまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "香月", "answers": [ "かつき", "かづき", "こうづき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 8%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "折口", "answers": [ "おりくち", "おりぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "岡林", "answers": [ "おかばやし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "磯山", "answers": [ "いそやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "紅葉", "answers": [ "あかば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "神津", "answers": [ "こうづ", "かみづ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "楠見", "answers": [ "くすみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "阿賀", "answers": [ "あが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "桑野", "answers": [ "くわの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "掛布", "answers": [ "かけふ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "園", "answers": [ "その" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "柴山", "answers": [ "しばやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "木島", "answers": [ "きじま", "きしま", "このしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 10%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "秋川", "answers": [ "あきかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "嬉野", "answers": [ "うれしの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 27%" },
	{ "question": "田尾", "answers": [ "たお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "住友", "answers": [ "すみとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "杉崎", "answers": [ "すぎさき", "すぎざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "宇梶", "answers": [ "うかじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "冷泉", "answers": [ "れいぜい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "成宮", "answers": [ "なりみや", "なるみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 32%" },
	{ "question": "水道橋", "answers": [ "すいどうばし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%" },
	{ "question": "姫野", "answers": [ "ひめの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "庄野", "answers": [ "しょうの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "出", "answers": [ "いで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "岩出", "answers": [ "いわで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "花井", "answers": [ "はない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "土門", "answers": [ "どもん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蒲池", "answers": [ "かまち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%" },
	{ "question": "全", "answers": [ "チョン", "ジョン", "ぜん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 10%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "浜野", "answers": [ "はまの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "地井", "answers": [ "ちい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "榊", "answers": [ "さかき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大家", "answers": [ "おおや", "おおか", "だいけ", "おおいえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%, 34%, 16%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "細井", "answers": [ "ほそい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊倉", "answers": [ "いくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "優香", "answers": [ "ゆうか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "安元", "answers": [ "やすもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "藤巻", "answers": [ "ふじまき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "釈", "answers": [ "しゃく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "金澤", "answers": [ "かなざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "角野", "answers": [ "かどの", "かくの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "蘆名", "answers": [ "あしな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "布", "answers": [ "ぬの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "尚樹", "answers": [ "しょうじゅ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "孟", "answers": [ "もう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%" },
	{ "question": "弘田", "answers": [ "ひろた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高乃", "answers": [ "たかの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宇津井", "answers": [ "うつい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "荒俣", "answers": [ "あらまた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "妻夫木", "answers": [ "つまぶき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "種村", "answers": [ "たねむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沢", "answers": [ "さわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "長与", "answers": [ "ながよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%" },
	{ "question": "浦和", "answers": [ "うらわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "山科", "answers": [ "やましな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%" },
	{ "question": "春田", "answers": [ "はるた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "立石", "answers": [ "たていし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "杉内", "answers": [ "すぎうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田子", "answers": [ "たご", "たこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "石", "answers": [ "せき", "いし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "川畑", "answers": [ "かわばた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "美優", "answers": [ "みゆう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "右近", "answers": [ "うこん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "舟橋", "answers": [ "ふなはし", "ふなばし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "戸谷", "answers": [ "とたに", "とや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "指原", "answers": [ "さしはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "巴", "answers": [ "ともえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%" },
	{ "question": "愛里", "answers": [ "あいり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "元木", "answers": [ "もとき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "園崎", "answers": [ "そのざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "斉木", "answers": [ "さいき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "入野", "answers": [ "いりの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "谷津", "answers": [ "やつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "千家", "answers": [ "せんけ", "せんげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "江波", "answers": [ "えなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%" },
	{ "question": "井沢", "answers": [ "いざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "祐穂", "answers": [ "ゆうほ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "米澤", "answers": [ "よねざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武者小路", "answers": [ "むしゃのこうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "御木本", "answers": [ "みきもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "常田", "answers": [ "ときた", "つねだ", "ときだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 10%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "日下部", "answers": [ "くさかべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "香山", "answers": [ "かやま", "こうやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "三吉", "answers": [ "みよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%" },
	{ "question": "北郷", "answers": [ "ほんごう", "きたごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "日村", "answers": [ "ひむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "押切", "answers": [ "おしきり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "谷中", "answers": [ "やなか", "たになか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 32%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "佃", "answers": [ "つくだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%" },
	{ "question": "松沢", "answers": [ "まつざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "馳", "answers": [ "はせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "豊原", "answers": [ "とよはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "塩川", "answers": [ "しおかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "木の実", "answers": [ "きのみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "市橋", "answers": [ "いちはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "向島", "answers": [ "むこうじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "名越", "answers": [ "なごし", "なこし", "なごや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 19%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "倉科", "answers": [ "くらしな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "音無", "answers": [ "おとなし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "昌", "answers": [ "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "宮里", "answers": [ "みやざと", "みやさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "藤澤", "answers": [ "ふじさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "城之内", "answers": [ "じょうのうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "五代", "answers": [ "ごだい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "浦田", "answers": [ "うらた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "秀", "answers": [ "しゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "若尾", "answers": [ "わかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "加護", "answers": [ "かご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "史", "answers": [ "し" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%" },
	{ "question": "人見", "answers": [ "ひとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "常盤", "answers": [ "ときわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%" },
	{ "question": "武上", "answers": [ "たけがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正田", "answers": [ "しょうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "工", "answers": [ "たくみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "倉持", "answers": [ "くらもち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大関", "answers": [ "おおぜき", "おおせき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "萬田", "answers": [ "まんだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "萩野", "answers": [ "はぎの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "河森", "answers": [ "かわもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浅尾", "answers": [ "あさお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "岩泉", "answers": [ "いわいずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "南田", "answers": [ "みなみだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "巽", "answers": [ "たつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%" },
	{ "question": "阿藤", "answers": [ "あとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻原", "answers": [ "あさはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "舟木", "answers": [ "ふなき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山東", "answers": [ "さんとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "坂崎", "answers": [ "さかざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "桐谷", "answers": [ "きりたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "阿波", "answers": [ "あわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "綾川", "answers": [ "あやかわ", "あやがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 24%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "六平", "answers": [ "むさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "船田", "answers": [ "ふなだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "羽多野", "answers": [ "はたの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "野本", "answers": [ "のもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鬼頭", "answers": [ "きとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小形", "answers": [ "おがた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "岩里", "answers": [ "いわさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小山内", "answers": [ "おさない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "龍山", "answers": [ "たつやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "兵藤", "answers": [ "ひょうどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一路", "answers": [ "いちろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%" },
	{ "question": "浅越", "answers": [ "あさごえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "横瀬", "answers": [ "よこせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%" },
	{ "question": "升", "answers": [ "ます" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "永作", "answers": [ "ながさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中畑", "answers": [ "なかはた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "杉野", "answers": [ "すぎの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千晶", "answers": [ "ちあき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "日明", "answers": [ "たちもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "河島", "answers": [ "かわしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "賀来", "answers": [ "かく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "阿久津", "answers": [ "あくつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鴨", "answers": [ "かも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%" },
	{ "question": "勝村", "answers": [ "かつむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "森野", "answers": [ "もりの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "三条西", "answers": [ "さんじょうにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "北沢", "answers": [ "きたざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浦野", "answers": [ "うらの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "市毛", "answers": [ "いちげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "矢井田", "answers": [ "やいだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "淡島", "answers": [ "あわしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "有島", "answers": [ "ありしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "木曽", "answers": [ "きそ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "川中", "answers": [ "かわなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "海江田", "answers": [ "かいえだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "豊山", "answers": [ "ゆたかやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%" },
	{ "question": "箕作", "answers": [ "みつくり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光石", "answers": [ "みついし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "丸岡", "answers": [ "まるおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "古橋", "answers": [ "ふるはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寺脇", "answers": [ "てらわき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "権藤", "answers": [ "ごんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大堀", "answers": [ "おおほり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "仁木", "answers": [ "にき", "にっき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "植草", "answers": [ "うえくさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "日出", "answers": [ "ひので" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "堀尾", "answers": [ "ほりお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "初音", "answers": [ "はつね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "末永", "answers": [ "すえなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "篠", "answers": [ "しの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "池辺", "answers": [ "いけべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "陸奥", "answers": [ "むつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "細江", "answers": [ "ほそえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%" },
	{ "question": "岡倉", "answers": [ "おかくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大坪", "answers": [ "おおつぼ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石渡", "answers": [ "いしわた", "いしわたり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "屋敷", "answers": [ "やしき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%" },
	{ "question": "北澤", "answers": [ "きたざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "河相", "answers": [ "かあい", "かわい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%, 39%" },
	{ "question": "重政", "answers": [ "しげまさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "斑鳩", "answers": [ "いかるが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "横光", "answers": [ "よこみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "室伏", "answers": [ "むろふし", "むろぶし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "笹木", "answers": [ "ささき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "駒田", "answers": [ "こまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "裴", "answers": [ "はい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "東地", "answers": [ "とうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "只野", "answers": [ "ただの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中塚", "answers": [ "なかつか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "北岡", "answers": [ "きたおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "愛新覚羅", "answers": [ "あいしんかくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小春", "answers": [ "こはる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "多久", "answers": [ "たく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "米長", "answers": [ "よねなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "多々良", "answers": [ "たたら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "景山", "answers": [ "かげやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "岡島", "answers": [ "おかじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "月岡", "answers": [ "つきおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "申", "answers": [ "しん", "シン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 33%" },
	{ "question": "小田切", "answers": [ "おだぎり", "おたぎり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "天知", "answers": [ "あまち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吾妻", "answers": [ "あづま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "安住", "answers": [ "あずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "由利", "answers": [ "ゆり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "舛田", "answers": [ "ますだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春野", "answers": [ "はるの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%" },
	{ "question": "門倉", "answers": [ "かどくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石倉", "answers": [ "いしくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "大海", "answers": [ "おおみ", "おおうみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "利光", "answers": [ "としみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%" },
	{ "question": "麻布", "answers": [ "あざぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "若井", "answers": [ "わかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "葉", "answers": [ "よう", "イエ", "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 5%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "松宮", "answers": [ "まつみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "紅音", "answers": [ "あかね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夏美", "answers": [ "なつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "三崎", "answers": [ "みさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%" },
	{ "question": "深澤", "answers": [ "ふかさわ", "ふかざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 30%" },
	{ "question": "蕭", "answers": [ "しょう", "しゅう", "しゅく", "シウ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 7%, 6%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "浪江", "answers": [ "なみえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "国東", "answers": [ "くにあずま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "矢立", "answers": [ "やたて" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "辻本", "answers": [ "つじもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高塚", "answers": [ "たかつか", "こうつか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "京野", "answers": [ "きょうの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "表", "answers": [ "おもて" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "雛形", "answers": [ "ひながた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "新堂", "answers": [ "しんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "北尾", "answers": [ "きたお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "飯尾", "answers": [ "いいお", "いのお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "秋葉", "answers": [ "あきば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "楢崎", "answers": [ "ならさき", "ならざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%, 47%" },
	{ "question": "世良", "answers": [ "せら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "花", "answers": [ "か" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "本部", "answers": [ "もとぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "小石川", "answers": [ "こいしかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "伊佐", "answers": [ "いさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "板谷", "answers": [ "いたや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "網野", "answers": [ "あみの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "長洲", "answers": [ "ながす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%" },
	{ "question": "時任", "answers": [ "ときとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "立野", "answers": [ "たての", "たちの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "古", "answers": [ "こ", "クー", "ふる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%, 12%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "又吉", "answers": [ "またよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "花村", "answers": [ "はなむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "柘植", "answers": [ "つげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%" },
	{ "question": "行", "answers": [ "ゆき", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "米内", "answers": [ "よない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉元", "answers": [ "よしもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%" },
	{ "question": "福圓", "answers": [ "ふくえん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "姫川", "answers": [ "ひめかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "友田", "answers": [ "ともだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "香西", "answers": [ "こうざい", "こうさい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%, 42%" },
	{ "question": "若杉", "answers": [ "わかすぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "牧田", "answers": [ "まきた", "まきだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "正力", "answers": [ "しょうりき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "里中", "answers": [ "さとなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小和田", "answers": [ "おわだ", "こわだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "麻丘", "answers": [ "あさおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朱里", "answers": [ "しゅり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "悠木", "answers": [ "ゆうき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "皆口", "answers": [ "みなぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "花沢", "answers": [ "はなさわ", "はなざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "竹達", "answers": [ "たけたつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "増谷", "answers": [ "ますたに", "ますや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "范", "answers": [ "はん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "直木", "answers": [ "なおき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "都志見", "answers": [ "つしみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武市", "answers": [ "たけち", "たけいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "宝田", "answers": [ "たからだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "大屋", "answers": [ "おおや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "浅丘", "answers": [ "あさおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "愛音", "answers": [ "あいね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "上島", "answers": [ "うえしま", "かみじま", "うえじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "間部", "answers": [ "まなべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "西平", "answers": [ "にしひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "徳丸", "answers": [ "とくまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "森安", "answers": [ "もりやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "谷岡", "answers": [ "たにおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "上泉", "answers": [ "かみいずみ", "うわいずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "枝野", "answers": [ "えだの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "飯野", "answers": [ "いいの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "飯沼", "answers": [ "いいぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "在原", "answers": [ "ありわら", "ありはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "合志", "answers": [ "ごうし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "一ノ関", "answers": [ "いちのせき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "前山田", "answers": [ "まえやまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田嶋", "answers": [ "たじま", "たしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "家長", "answers": [ "いえなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%" },
	{ "question": "新海", "answers": [ "しんかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "沢井", "answers": [ "さわい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "池端", "answers": [ "いけはた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春香", "answers": [ "はるか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 22%" },
	{ "question": "竹富", "answers": [ "たけとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "和久井", "answers": [ "わくい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "古内", "answers": [ "ふるうち", "こうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "沢尻", "answers": [ "さわじり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "厳", "answers": [ "げん", "オム" ], "comment": "Frequency: 50%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "江利", "answers": [ "えり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蛯原", "answers": [ "えびはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宣", "answers": [ "ソン", "せん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "安永", "answers": [ "やすなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "立浪", "answers": [ "たつなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "白土", "answers": [ "しらと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "庄", "answers": [ "しょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%" },
	{ "question": "鹿賀", "answers": [ "かが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "尾山", "answers": [ "おやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "二葉", "answers": [ "ふたば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%" },
	{ "question": "小谷野", "answers": [ "こやの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "盛田", "answers": [ "もりた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "森内", "answers": [ "もりうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "曽", "answers": [ "そう", "そ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "桐本", "answers": [ "きりもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "粕谷", "answers": [ "かすや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "新居", "answers": [ "あらい", "にい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "大知", "answers": [ "おおち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "八嶋", "answers": [ "やしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光浦", "answers": [ "みつうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "新渡戸", "answers": [ "にとべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長友", "answers": [ "ながとも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "川谷", "answers": [ "かわたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小田部", "answers": [ "おたべ", "こたべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 32%" },
	{ "question": "内川", "answers": [ "うちかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "会田", "answers": [ "あいだ", "あいた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "駒込", "answers": [ "こまごめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "柳本", "answers": [ "やなぎもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "百田", "answers": [ "ももた", "ひゃくた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "沢海", "answers": [ "そうみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "天草", "answers": [ "あまくさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松代", "answers": [ "まつよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "国見", "answers": [ "くにみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 36%" },
	{ "question": "赤平", "answers": [ "あかひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%" },
	{ "question": "松澤", "answers": [ "まつざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富澤", "answers": [ "とみざわ", "とみさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "末松", "answers": [ "すえまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "金尾", "answers": [ "かなお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "福", "answers": [ "ふく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "後藤田", "answers": [ "ごとうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小沼", "answers": [ "こぬま", "おぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%, 44%" },
	{ "question": "叶", "answers": [ "かのう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "木場", "answers": [ "きば", "こば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "頭師", "answers": [ "ずし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊秩", "answers": [ "いぢち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高市", "answers": [ "たかいち", "たけち", "たかち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "亀石", "answers": [ "かめいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "乙羽", "answers": [ "おとわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "井森", "answers": [ "いもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "石上", "answers": [ "いしがみ", "いそのかみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%, 37%" },
	{ "question": "南雲", "answers": [ "なぐも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "猪瀬", "answers": [ "いのせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "斉", "answers": [ "せい", "さい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "上大岡", "answers": [ "かみおおおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "寺沢", "answers": [ "てらさわ", "てらざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "霜月", "answers": [ "しもつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喜多川", "answers": [ "きたがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "川又", "answers": [ "かわまた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長南", "answers": [ "ちょうなん", "おさなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "釜本", "answers": [ "かまもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "御影", "answers": [ "みかげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%" },
	{ "question": "大豊", "answers": [ "たいほう", "おおゆたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 36%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "宮坂", "answers": [ "みやさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "峯岸", "answers": [ "みねぎし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "正宗", "answers": [ "まさむね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%" },
	{ "question": "宇徳", "answers": [ "うとく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "安野", "answers": [ "あんの", "やすの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "安宅", "answers": [ "あたか", "あたぎ", "あたく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%, 30%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "政次", "answers": [ "まさつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "東浦", "answers": [ "ひがしうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "垂井", "answers": [ "たるい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "湯原", "answers": [ "ゆはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "榎木", "answers": [ "えのき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "楳図", "answers": [ "うめず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "海田", "answers": [ "かいだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "柳瀬", "answers": [ "やなせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "戸浦", "answers": [ "とうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小籔", "answers": [ "こやぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鵜飼", "answers": [ "うかい", "うがい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "河北", "answers": [ "かわきた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%" },
	{ "question": "向谷", "answers": [ "むかいや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "神", "answers": [ "じん", "かみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "扇", "answers": [ "おおぎ", "おうぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "井伏", "answers": [ "いぶせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "粟津", "answers": [ "あわづ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "梨花", "answers": [ "りか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%" },
	{ "question": "麻実", "answers": [ "あさみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%" },
	{ "question": "七飯", "answers": [ "ななえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "松重", "answers": [ "まつしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "柴原", "answers": [ "しばはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "国仲", "answers": [ "くになか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "楠本", "answers": [ "くすもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有野", "answers": [ "ありの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "満仲", "answers": [ "まんなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "久司", "answers": [ "くし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "早稲田", "answers": [ "わせだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 24%" },
	{ "question": "山浦", "answers": [ "やまうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "古島", "answers": [ "ふるしま", "こじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "竹脇", "answers": [ "たけわき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "末吉", "answers": [ "すえよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "国枝", "answers": [ "くにえだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "池部", "answers": [ "いけべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "伊井", "answers": [ "いい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千代丸", "answers": [ "ちよまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "重成", "answers": [ "しげなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "松中", "answers": [ "まつなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "阪東", "answers": [ "ばんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "実相寺", "answers": [ "じっそうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桐野", "answers": [ "きりの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有坂", "answers": [ "ありさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春海", "answers": [ "はるみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%" },
	{ "question": "逸見", "answers": [ "へんみ", "いつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "名波", "answers": [ "ななみ", "なわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "伊庭", "answers": [ "いば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "師岡", "answers": [ "もろおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%" },
	{ "question": "十河", "answers": [ "そごう", "とごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "村主", "answers": [ "すぐり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桑谷", "answers": [ "くわたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "甘利", "answers": [ "あまり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有里", "answers": [ "ゆうり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "八十", "answers": [ "やそ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "真咲", "answers": [ "まさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%" },
	{ "question": "西浦", "answers": [ "にしうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "永倉", "answers": [ "ながくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "咲野", "answers": [ "さくや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "郷原", "answers": [ "ごうはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "北乃", "answers": [ "きたの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明坂", "answers": [ "あけさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "逢沢", "answers": [ "あいざわ", "あいさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%, 49%" },
	{ "question": "佐江", "answers": [ "さえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "達川", "answers": [ "たつかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "越路", "answers": [ "こしじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "相葉", "answers": [ "あいば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "舛添", "answers": [ "ますぞえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "半藤", "answers": [ "はんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "友部", "answers": [ "ともべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%" },
	{ "question": "久住", "answers": [ "くすみ", "くずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "立", "answers": [ "りつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "二川", "answers": [ "ふたがわ", "にかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "川久保", "answers": [ "かわくぼ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊瀬", "answers": [ "いせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大貴", "answers": [ "だいき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "長生", "answers": [ "ながお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "綱島", "answers": [ "つなしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%" },
	{ "question": "佐治", "answers": [ "さじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "晏", "answers": [ "ヤン", "あん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "竜崎", "answers": [ "りゅうざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "螢", "answers": [ "ほたる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%" },
	{ "question": "津野", "answers": [ "つの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%" },
	{ "question": "魁皇", "answers": [ "かいおう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長瀞", "answers": [ "ながとろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "村越", "answers": [ "むらこし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中崎", "answers": [ "なかざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "梅沢", "answers": [ "うめざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "宇田川", "answers": [ "うだがわ", "うたがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "生沢", "answers": [ "いくざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田名部", "answers": [ "たなぶ", "たなべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 51%, 41%" },
	{ "question": "神尾", "answers": [ "かみお", "かんお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "大須賀", "answers": [ "おおすが", "おおすか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "荒", "answers": [ "あら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "麻倉", "answers": [ "あさくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "五戸", "answers": [ "ごのへ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "吹石", "answers": [ "ふきいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "徳富", "answers": [ "とくとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "菅谷", "answers": [ "すがや", "すがたに", "すげのや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 20%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "小塚", "answers": [ "こづか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "音羽", "answers": [ "おとわ", "おとは" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "円舘", "answers": [ "えんだて" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "上本", "answers": [ "うえもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%" },
	{ "question": "赤池", "answers": [ "あかいけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 42%" },
	{ "question": "野比", "answers": [ "のび" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仁藤", "answers": [ "にとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "殿山", "answers": [ "とのやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "武見", "answers": [ "たけみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%" },
	{ "question": "大道", "answers": [ "おおみち", "だいどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "番", "answers": [ "ばん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%" },
	{ "question": "旦", "answers": [ "だん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "吉成", "answers": [ "よしなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 36%" },
	{ "question": "松雪", "answers": [ "まつゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "白洲", "answers": [ "しらす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "志倉", "answers": [ "しくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "古関", "answers": [ "こせき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "三雲", "answers": [ "みくも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "幣原", "answers": [ "しではら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小村", "answers": [ "こむら", "おむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 26%" },
	{ "question": "如月", "answers": [ "きさらぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "福崎", "answers": [ "ふくざき", "ふくさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "武蔵丸", "answers": [ "むさしまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "牧瀬", "answers": [ "まきせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "本因坊", "answers": [ "ほんいんぼう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "熊沢", "answers": [ "くまざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "川添", "answers": [ "かわぞえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "淡谷", "answers": [ "あわや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寿美", "answers": [ "すみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%" },
	{ "question": "正司", "answers": [ "しょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%" },
	{ "question": "門司", "answers": [ "もんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "物部", "answers": [ "もののべ", "ものべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "月光", "answers": [ "つきみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "建部", "answers": [ "たけべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "子門", "answers": [ "しもん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桜沢", "answers": [ "さくらざわ", "おうさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 29%" },
	{ "question": "近野", "answers": [ "こんの", "ちかの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 41%" },
	{ "question": "大迫", "answers": [ "おおさこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "役", "answers": [ "えん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芦原", "answers": [ "あしはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "凌", "answers": [ "りょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "元長", "answers": [ "もとなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "瑞山", "answers": [ "みずやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "東川", "answers": [ "ひがしかわ", "ひがしがわ", "とうかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%, 17%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "前島", "answers": [ "まえじま", "まえしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "中平", "answers": [ "なかひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田野", "answers": [ "たの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%" },
	{ "question": "古手川", "answers": [ "こてがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "岸谷", "answers": [ "きしたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浦山", "answers": [ "うらやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "赤間", "answers": [ "あかま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "綿貫", "answers": [ "わたぬき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "間島", "answers": [ "まじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "毒蝮", "answers": [ "どくまむし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "下地", "answers": [ "しもじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "小磯", "answers": [ "こいそ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "江上", "answers": [ "えがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有沢", "answers": [ "ありさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%" },
	{ "question": "北谷", "answers": [ "きたたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "吉江", "answers": [ "よしえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "吹越", "answers": [ "ふきこし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "塚地", "answers": [ "つかじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "家弓", "answers": [ "かゆみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弥永", "answers": [ "やなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "八名", "answers": [ "やな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "本名", "answers": [ "ほんな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "藤咲", "answers": [ "ふじさき", "ふじさく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "萱野", "answers": [ "かやの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "金石", "answers": [ "かねいし", "かないし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "岩代", "answers": [ "いわしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "時枝", "answers": [ "ときえだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "堀切", "answers": [ "ほりきり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 36%" },
	{ "question": "鶴橋", "answers": [ "つるはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "行定", "answers": [ "ゆきさだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宝生", "answers": [ "ほうしょう", "ほうじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "金春", "answers": [ "こんぱる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "嘉納", "answers": [ "かのう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "岩隈", "answers": [ "いわくま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "池畑", "answers": [ "いけはた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "村重", "answers": [ "むらしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "夢枕", "answers": [ "ゆめまくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田所", "answers": [ "たどころ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "末次", "answers": [ "すえつぐ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "岡元", "answers": [ "おかもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有栖川宮", "answers": [ "ありすがわのみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "相武", "answers": [ "あいぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "一二三", "answers": [ "ひふみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "茶屋町", "answers": [ "ちゃやまち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "福沢", "answers": [ "ふくざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竹腰", "answers": [ "たけのこし", "たけこし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "江森", "answers": [ "えもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "臼田", "answers": [ "うすだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "知里", "answers": [ "ちり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%" },
	{ "question": "綿引", "answers": [ "わたびき", "わたひき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "横路", "answers": [ "よこみち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "南方", "answers": [ "みなかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "降旗", "answers": [ "ふるはた", "ふりはた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "古代", "answers": [ "こだい", "こしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 40%" },
	{ "question": "香田", "answers": [ "こうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "川平", "answers": [ "かびら", "かわひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 16%" },
	{ "question": "天心", "answers": [ "てんしん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "南井", "answers": [ "みない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "水川", "answers": [ "みずかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "深町", "answers": [ "ふかまち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "私市", "answers": [ "きさいち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%" },
	{ "question": "市井", "answers": [ "いちい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "玉城", "answers": [ "たまき", "たましろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 24%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "百瀬", "answers": [ "ももせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久富", "answers": [ "ひさとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "野平", "answers": [ "のひら", "のだいら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "瀧川", "answers": [ "たきがわ", "たきかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 13%" },
	{ "question": "金月", "answers": [ "きんげつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "村木", "answers": [ "むらき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高本", "answers": [ "たかもと", "こうもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "汐路", "answers": [ "しおじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小暮", "answers": [ "こぐれ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寧", "answers": [ "ねい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "下郷", "answers": [ "しもざと", "しもごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "江坂", "answers": [ "えさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "三角", "answers": [ "みすみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%" },
	{ "question": "藤末", "answers": [ "ふじすえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春畑", "answers": [ "はるはた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "根上", "answers": [ "ねがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "西口", "answers": [ "にしぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "渡嘉敷", "answers": [ "とかしき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%" },
	{ "question": "醍醐", "answers": [ "だいご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 71%" },
	{ "question": "谷繁", "answers": [ "たにしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "左右田", "answers": [ "そうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "志水", "answers": [ "しみず", "しみづ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%, 24%" },
	{ "question": "高良", "answers": [ "こうら", "たから" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "石津", "answers": [ "いしづ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "錦", "answers": [ "にしき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "羽後", "answers": [ "うご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "四方", "answers": [ "よも", "しかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "馬淵", "answers": [ "まぶち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春名", "answers": [ "はるな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "坪田", "answers": [ "つぼた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "項", "answers": [ "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "折原", "answers": [ "おりはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "閻", "answers": [ "えん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "天川", "answers": [ "あまかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%" },
	{ "question": "岩内", "answers": [ "いわうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "三間", "answers": [ "みま", "みつま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "田崎", "answers": [ "たさき", "たざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 37%" },
	{ "question": "笹路", "answers": [ "ささじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梶浦", "answers": [ "かじうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "滝澤", "answers": [ "たきざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "草柳", "answers": [ "くさやなぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鏡", "answers": [ "かがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "一城", "answers": [ "いちじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千代", "answers": [ "ちよ", "せんだい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "三澤", "answers": [ "みさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "徳重", "answers": [ "とくしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "宅麻", "answers": [ "たくま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鷹森", "answers": [ "たかもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小鹿", "answers": [ "こじか", "おしか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "黒井", "answers": [ "くろい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%" },
	{ "question": "楠瀬", "answers": [ "くすのせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真珠", "answers": [ "しんじゅ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "木津", "answers": [ "きづ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "涌井", "answers": [ "わくい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "夢野", "answers": [ "ゆめの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梨田", "answers": [ "なしだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "永原", "answers": [ "ながはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "金野", "answers": [ "こんの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "加戸", "answers": [ "かと", "かど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "若宮", "answers": [ "わかみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "淀川", "answers": [ "よどがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "谷田部", "answers": [ "やたべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "坂野", "answers": [ "ばんの", "さかの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 45%" },
	{ "question": "筈見", "answers": [ "はずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "月野", "answers": [ "つきの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "相島", "answers": [ "あいじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "美雪", "answers": [ "みゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "御徒町", "answers": [ "おかちまち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%" },
	{ "question": "増沢", "answers": [ "ますざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寺崎", "answers": [ "てらさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仙谷", "answers": [ "せんごく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "国吉", "answers": [ "くによし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "天津", "answers": [ "あまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "脇", "answers": [ "わき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山木", "answers": [ "やまき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "牧原", "answers": [ "まきはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "本阿弥", "answers": [ "ほんあみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広中", "answers": [ "ひろなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "冨樫", "answers": [ "とがし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "坪倉", "answers": [ "つぼくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "楠田", "answers": [ "くすだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久我", "answers": [ "くが", "こが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 27%" },
	{ "question": "荘司", "answers": [ "しょうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "定", "answers": [ "じょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "蒔田", "answers": [ "まいた", "まきた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "賀川", "answers": [ "かがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大出", "answers": [ "おおいで", "おおで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "山像", "answers": [ "やまがた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "向山", "answers": [ "むこうやま", "むかいやま", "さきやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%, 24%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "宮台", "answers": [ "みやだい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "道重", "answers": [ "みちしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "富司", "answers": [ "ふじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "四宮", "answers": [ "しのみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "河崎", "answers": [ "かわさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "江戸", "answers": [ "えど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "筑前", "answers": [ "ちくぜん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "利重", "answers": [ "りじゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%" },
	{ "question": "三咲", "answers": [ "みさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%" },
	{ "question": "笹岡", "answers": [ "ささおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亀梨", "answers": [ "かめなし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "上木", "answers": [ "かみき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大神", "answers": [ "おおがみ", "おおが", "おおみわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 58%, 35%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "井端", "answers": [ "いばた", "いはた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 20%" },
	{ "question": "井ノ原", "answers": [ "いのはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真鶴", "answers": [ "まなづる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "蛍原", "answers": [ "ほとはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "穂高", "answers": [ "ほだか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%" },
	{ "question": "南里", "answers": [ "なんり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "南波", "answers": [ "なんば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仲田", "answers": [ "なかだ", "なかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 36%" },
	{ "question": "程", "answers": [ "てい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%" },
	{ "question": "鶴間", "answers": [ "つるま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%" },
	{ "question": "佐戸井", "answers": [ "さとい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "糸", "answers": [ "いと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "石堂", "answers": [ "いしどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "大間", "answers": [ "おおま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%" },
	{ "question": "宮根", "answers": [ "みやね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "嵯峨", "answers": [ "さが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "熊井", "answers": [ "くまい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石立", "answers": [ "いしだて" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "雪村", "answers": [ "ゆきむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "円山", "answers": [ "まるやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%" },
	{ "question": "丸藤", "answers": [ "まるふじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "遠近", "answers": [ "とおちか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "木野", "answers": [ "きの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "三川", "answers": [ "みかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%" },
	{ "question": "三重野", "answers": [ "みえの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "玉山", "answers": [ "たまやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "多田野", "answers": [ "ただの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "幸徳", "answers": [ "こうとく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "菊谷", "answers": [ "きくや", "きくたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "音", "answers": [ "おと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "芳本", "answers": [ "よしもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "保利", "answers": [ "ほり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "羽毛田", "answers": [ "はけた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "葉加瀬", "answers": [ "はかせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竹若", "answers": [ "たけわか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春馬", "answers": [ "はるま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "炎", "answers": [ "ほのお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "嘉手納", "answers": [ "かてな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 22%" },
	{ "question": "矢代", "answers": [ "やしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "引田", "answers": [ "ひきた", "ひけた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "徳大寺", "answers": [ "とくだいじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "澄川", "answers": [ "すみかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "清木場", "answers": [ "きよきば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "我那覇", "answers": [ "がなは" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "今谷", "answers": [ "いまたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "安生", "answers": [ "あんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 38%" },
	{ "question": "花輪", "answers": [ "はなわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "奈良岡", "answers": [ "ならおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大岩", "answers": [ "おおいわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "愛河", "answers": [ "あいかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大和屋", "answers": [ "やまとや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "薬師寺", "answers": [ "やくしじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "升田", "answers": [ "ますだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真下", "answers": [ "ましも", "ました" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "塩山", "answers": [ "しおやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%" },
	{ "question": "向坂", "answers": [ "さきさか", "こうさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "貫地谷", "answers": [ "かんじや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "湯山", "answers": [ "ゆやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "水沼", "answers": [ "みずぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "水", "answers": [ "みず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%" },
	{ "question": "猫", "answers": [ "ねこ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "天山", "answers": [ "てんざん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "城田", "answers": [ "しろた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "白根", "answers": [ "しらね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "神前", "answers": [ "こうさき", "かんざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "荻生", "answers": [ "おぎゅう", "おぎう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "桑折", "answers": [ "こおり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 22%" },
	{ "question": "神河", "answers": [ "かみかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "湯屋", "answers": [ "ゆや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "増本", "answers": [ "ますもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "野尻", "answers": [ "のじり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "高部", "answers": [ "たかべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奥寺", "answers": [ "おくでら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "澪", "answers": [ "みお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "目白", "answers": [ "めじろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "豊浦", "answers": [ "とようら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "原西", "answers": [ "はらにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高口", "answers": [ "たかぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "國村", "answers": [ "くにむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "植芝", "answers": [ "うえしば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "利根", "answers": [ "とね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 36%" },
	{ "question": "椎葉", "answers": [ "しいば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "堅田", "answers": [ "かただ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "錦野", "answers": [ "にしきの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "白倉", "answers": [ "しらくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "琴欧洲", "answers": [ "ことおうしゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "加賀美", "answers": [ "かがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "開高", "answers": [ "かいこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "岡井", "answers": [ "おかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "穴井", "answers": [ "あない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "河南", "answers": [ "かなん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "清浦", "answers": [ "きようら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大鳥", "answers": [ "おおとり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一龍斎", "answers": [ "いちりゅうさい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "愛乃", "answers": [ "あいの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "本村", "answers": [ "もとむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "藤代", "answers": [ "ふじしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%" },
	{ "question": "薛", "answers": [ "せつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "杉江", "answers": [ "すぎえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "北里", "answers": [ "きたざと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "河竹", "answers": [ "かわたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鏑木", "answers": [ "かぶらき", "かぶらぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 68%, 32%" },
	{ "question": "大本", "answers": [ "おおもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大畠", "answers": [ "おおはた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "荒巻", "answers": [ "あらまき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "廣", "answers": [ "ひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 11%" },
	{ "question": "七生", "answers": [ "ななお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "御船", "answers": [ "みふね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "松倉", "answers": [ "まつくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "本上", "answers": [ "ほんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "名倉", "answers": [ "なぐら", "なくら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "高戸", "answers": [ "たかと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "涼風", "answers": [ "すずかぜ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "曲亭", "answers": [ "きょくてい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "君塚", "answers": [ "きみづか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和晃", "answers": [ "かつひかり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "平群", "answers": [ "へぐり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "羽場", "answers": [ "はば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "辻谷", "answers": [ "つじたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高中", "answers": [ "たかなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "小松原", "answers": [ "こまつばら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉富", "answers": [ "よしとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 28%" },
	{ "question": "天満", "answers": [ "てんま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "清里", "answers": [ "きよさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "村治", "answers": [ "むらじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "広沢", "answers": [ "ひろさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%" },
	{ "question": "妃乃", "answers": [ "ひの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鷹司", "answers": [ "たかつかさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "蔵原", "answers": [ "くらはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "国広", "answers": [ "くにひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "桐島", "answers": [ "きりしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "河辺", "answers": [ "かわべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%" },
	{ "question": "河口", "answers": [ "かわぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "岡江", "answers": [ "おかえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "有沙", "answers": [ "ありさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "増崎", "answers": [ "ますざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "巻", "answers": [ "まき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "日馬富士", "answers": [ "はるまふじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大道寺", "answers": [ "だいどうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "染谷", "answers": [ "そめや", "そめたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 48%" },
	{ "question": "国定", "answers": [ "くにさだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "神原", "answers": [ "かんばら", "かみはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "尾美", "answers": [ "おみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仰木", "answers": [ "おおぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "江尻", "answers": [ "えじり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "朝吹", "answers": [ "あさぶき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明田川", "answers": [ "あけたがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉武", "answers": [ "よしたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "村下", "answers": [ "むらした" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "杉森", "answers": [ "すぎもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "常", "answers": [ "じょう", "つね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "北田", "answers": [ "きただ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻木", "answers": [ "あさぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "国光", "answers": [ "くにみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "月島", "answers": [ "つきしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "鷲崎", "answers": [ "わしざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "森嶋", "answers": [ "もりしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "肥後", "answers": [ "ひご" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鳴瀬", "answers": [ "なるせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寺西", "answers": [ "てらにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田の中", "answers": [ "たのなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "国本", "answers": [ "くにもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "海老原", "answers": [ "えびはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "一ノ瀬", "answers": [ "いちのせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蓮", "answers": [ "はす", "れん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "麻央", "answers": [ "まお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 24%" },
	{ "question": "善", "answers": [ "ぜん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 19%" },
	{ "question": "水内", "answers": [ "みずうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "澤井", "answers": [ "さわい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "麻宮", "answers": [ "あさみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "多聞", "answers": [ "たもん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "光岡", "answers": [ "みつおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "松金", "answers": [ "まつかね", "まつがね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "弘中", "answers": [ "ひろなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "千代大海", "answers": [ "ちよたいかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "喜田", "answers": [ "きだ", "きた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "青江", "answers": [ "あおえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "青井", "answers": [ "あおい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%" },
	{ "question": "玉村", "answers": [ "たまむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "小竹", "answers": [ "こたけ", "おたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "八重樫", "answers": [ "やえがし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三森", "answers": [ "みもり", "みつもり", "さんもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 11%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "信時", "answers": [ "のぶとき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 72%" },
	{ "question": "梨本", "answers": [ "なしもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "上月", "answers": [ "こうづき", "こうつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "岩間", "answers": [ "いわま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 84%" },
	{ "question": "出光", "answers": [ "いでみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "野木", "answers": [ "のぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "幹本", "answers": [ "みきもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "益岡", "answers": [ "ますおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高谷", "answers": [ "たかや", "たかたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "曽田", "answers": [ "そだ", "そた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "川路", "answers": [ "かわじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "小熊", "answers": [ "おぐま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "新富", "answers": [ "しんとみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "岩切", "answers": [ "いわきり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%" },
	{ "question": "馬渕", "answers": [ "まぶち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "廣木", "answers": [ "ひろき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仲本", "answers": [ "なかもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田久保", "answers": [ "たくぼ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "倉石", "answers": [ "くらいし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石澤", "answers": [ "いしざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "早希", "answers": [ "さき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "神川", "answers": [ "かみかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "成海", "answers": [ "なるみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "豊嶋", "answers": [ "とよしま", "てしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "鈴音", "answers": [ "すずね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%" },
	{ "question": "顧", "answers": [ "こ", "グー" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "車", "answers": [ "くるま", "チャ", "しゃ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 25%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "犬童", "answers": [ "いぬどう", "いんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "今里", "answers": [ "いまざと", "いまさと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "横峯", "answers": [ "よこみね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "福間", "answers": [ "ふくま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%" },
	{ "question": "深尾", "answers": [ "ふかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小六", "answers": [ "ころく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "可愛", "answers": [ "かわい", "かあい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "上沼", "answers": [ "かみぬま", "うえぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "興津", "answers": [ "おきつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "両津", "answers": [ "りょうつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "森尾", "answers": [ "もりお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松風", "answers": [ "まつかぜ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鈴井", "answers": [ "すずい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "木幡", "answers": [ "こばた", "こわた", "こはた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 43%, 29%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "青空", "answers": [ "あおぞら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%" },
	{ "question": "富谷", "answers": [ "とみや", "とみたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "高安", "answers": [ "たかやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 33%" },
	{ "question": "東雲", "answers": [ "しののめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "恩納", "answers": [ "おんな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "牧村", "answers": [ "まきむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "日暮", "answers": [ "ひぐらし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "錦戸", "answers": [ "にしきど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "五所", "answers": [ "ごしょ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "鴻上", "answers": [ "こうかみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梅本", "answers": [ "うめもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "雨森", "answers": [ "あめのもり", "あまもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "延", "answers": [ "えん", "ヨン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "中城", "answers": [ "なかじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "森島", "answers": [ "もりしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "渕崎", "answers": [ "ふちざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "新沼", "answers": [ "にいぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佐良", "answers": [ "さがら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "草鹿", "answers": [ "くさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "国頭", "answers": [ "くにとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "羅", "answers": [ "ら", "ナ", "ラ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 20%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "米光", "answers": [ "よねみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "本広", "answers": [ "もとひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "柱谷", "answers": [ "はしらたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "孔", "answers": [ "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久米田", "answers": [ "くめた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%" },
	{ "question": "小野塚", "answers": [ "おのづか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大宅", "answers": [ "おおや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "瓜生", "answers": [ "うりゅう", "うりう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "今江", "answers": [ "いまえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "稲本", "answers": [ "いなもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "白子", "answers": [ "しらこ", "はくし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "山縣", "answers": [ "やまがた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "古井", "answers": [ "ふるい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "二階", "answers": [ "にかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "辻元", "answers": [ "つじもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竹野内", "answers": [ "たけのうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "世耕", "answers": [ "せこう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小見川", "answers": [ "おみがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "市田", "answers": [ "いちだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "愛原", "answers": [ "あいはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "重宗", "answers": [ "しげむね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "播磨", "answers": [ "はりま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "吉水", "answers": [ "よしみず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "村西", "answers": [ "むらにし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "増井", "answers": [ "ますい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "恒松", "answers": [ "つねまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三笑亭", "answers": [ "さんしょうてい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "河瀬", "answers": [ "かわせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%" },
	{ "question": "綾波", "answers": [ "あやなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "赤尾", "answers": [ "あかお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "左近", "answers": [ "さこん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "小町", "answers": [ "こまち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "御宿", "answers": [ "みしゅく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "任", "answers": [ "じん", "にん", "セリナ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%, 15%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "江木", "answers": [ "えぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "芦沢", "answers": [ "あしざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "玉造", "answers": [ "たまつくり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "大曲", "answers": [ "おおまがり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "若乃花", "answers": [ "わかのはな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "六郷", "answers": [ "ろくごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "屋代", "answers": [ "やしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 53%" },
	{ "question": "中越", "answers": [ "なかごし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "栃東", "answers": [ "とちあずま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "月丘", "answers": [ "つきおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "武野", "answers": [ "たけの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "今中", "answers": [ "いまなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "井岡", "answers": [ "いおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桃", "answers": [ "もも" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "彩芽", "answers": [ "あやめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 22%" },
	{ "question": "亜門", "answers": [ "あもん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "若村", "answers": [ "わかむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "棟方", "answers": [ "むなかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仲川", "answers": [ "なかがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "黒瀬", "answers": [ "くろせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "海老沢", "answers": [ "えびさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "磯辺", "answers": [ "いそべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朝加", "answers": [ "あさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清成", "answers": [ "きよなり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 39%" },
	{ "question": "新納", "answers": [ "にいろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "鹿取", "answers": [ "かとり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "井本", "answers": [ "いもと", "いのもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "生稲", "answers": [ "いくいな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "日根野", "answers": [ "ひねの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 47%" },
	{ "question": "早島", "answers": [ "はやしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "泉州", "answers": [ "せんしゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "小中", "answers": [ "こなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "大桑", "answers": [ "おおくわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "増村", "answers": [ "ますむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "北都", "answers": [ "ほくと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "中内", "answers": [ "なかうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "戸崎", "answers": [ "とさき", "とざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "梅垣", "answers": [ "うめがき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石住", "answers": [ "いしずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "赤瀬川", "answers": [ "あかせがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "古山", "answers": [ "ふるやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "西園", "answers": [ "にしぞの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "知花", "answers": [ "ちばな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%" },
	{ "question": "武智", "answers": [ "たけち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "須貝", "answers": [ "すがい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佐分利", "answers": [ "さぶり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "郡司", "answers": [ "ぐんじ", "ぐんし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "桑山", "answers": [ "くわやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "川淵", "answers": [ "かわぶち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "神木", "answers": [ "かみき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "葛山", "answers": [ "かつらやま", "くずやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "久代", "answers": [ "くしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "東中野", "answers": [ "ひがしなかの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "門川", "answers": [ "かどかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "分部", "answers": [ "わけべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "脇田", "answers": [ "わきた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "米津", "answers": [ "よねきつ", "よねつ", "よねづ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 5%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "町山", "answers": [ "まちやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "栃錦", "answers": [ "とちにしき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "土山", "answers": [ "つちやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%" },
	{ "question": "武村", "answers": [ "たけむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "角居", "answers": [ "すみい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "和宮", "answers": [ "かずのみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奥菜", "answers": [ "おきな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "岩浪", "answers": [ "いわなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "植", "answers": [ "うえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "今津", "answers": [ "いまず", "いまづ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 31%, 23%" },
	{ "question": "野宮", "answers": [ "のみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "津久井", "answers": [ "つくい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高林", "answers": [ "たかばやし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "児嶋", "answers": [ "こじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "柿沼", "answers": [ "かきぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "奥貫", "answers": [ "おくぬき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "比呂", "answers": [ "ひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "和知", "answers": [ "わち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "竹久", "answers": [ "たけひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "瀬田", "answers": [ "せた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "黒谷", "answers": [ "くろたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "上坂", "answers": [ "うえさか", "かみさか", "こうさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%, 44%, 11%" },
	{ "question": "井浦", "answers": [ "いうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "吉雄", "answers": [ "よしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 13%" },
	{ "question": "六月", "answers": [ "むつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%" },
	{ "question": "高根沢", "answers": [ "たかねざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "栄村", "answers": [ "さかえむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "桃咲", "answers": [ "ももさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中馬", "answers": [ "ちゅうま", "ちゅうまん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 34%" },
	{ "question": "貝原", "answers": [ "かいばら", "かいはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "常光", "answers": [ "つねみつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 17%" },
	{ "question": "沙羅", "answers": [ "さら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 16%" },
	{ "question": "元山", "answers": [ "もとやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "須磨", "answers": [ "すま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%" },
	{ "question": "小岩", "answers": [ "こいわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "阿武", "answers": [ "あんの", "あぶ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "横澤", "answers": [ "よこざわ", "よこさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 15%" },
	{ "question": "藤生", "answers": [ "ふじき", "ふじう", "ふじお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 17%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "冨士", "answers": [ "ふじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "平島", "answers": [ "ひらしま", "ひらじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 61%, 18%" },
	{ "question": "西森", "answers": [ "にしもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "並樹", "answers": [ "なみき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長塚", "answers": [ "ながつか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "永岡", "answers": [ "ながおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "首藤", "answers": [ "しゅとう", "しゅどう", "すとう", "すどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 22%, 22%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "河越", "answers": [ "かわごえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "牛田", "answers": [ "うしだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 56%" },
	{ "question": "今岡", "answers": [ "いまおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三塚", "answers": [ "みつづか", "みつか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "水本", "answers": [ "みずもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 99%" },
	{ "question": "二岡", "answers": [ "におか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "段田", "answers": [ "だんた", "だんだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "佐瀬", "answers": [ "させ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "顔", "answers": [ "がん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "樫井", "answers": [ "かしい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "嘉島", "answers": [ "かしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "侯", "answers": [ "ホウ", "こう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 38%" },
	{ "question": "三津谷", "answers": [ "みつや", "みつたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "未知", "answers": [ "みち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "松浪", "answers": [ "まつなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "櫻内", "answers": [ "さくらうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "海原", "answers": [ "かいばら", "うなばら", "うみはら", "かいはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 11%, 5%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "尾高", "answers": [ "おだか", "おたか", "すえたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 32%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "猪口", "answers": [ "いのぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "伊坂", "answers": [ "いさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "姉小路", "answers": [ "あねがこうじ", "あねこうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "雪広", "answers": [ "ゆきひろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 22%" },
	{ "question": "長安", "answers": [ "ながやす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "宮寺", "answers": [ "みやでら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "御厨", "answers": [ "みくりや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 87%" },
	{ "question": "福嶋", "answers": [ "ふくしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "羽賀", "answers": [ "はが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "永川", "answers": [ "ながかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%" },
	{ "question": "谷内", "answers": [ "たにうち", "やち", "やない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%, 41%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "小阪", "answers": [ "こさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "佳那", "answers": [ "かな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "深雪", "answers": [ "みゆき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%" },
	{ "question": "下谷", "answers": [ "しもたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "待田", "answers": [ "まちだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "広井", "answers": [ "ひろい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "響", "answers": [ "ひびき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 55%" },
	{ "question": "苫米地", "answers": [ "とまべち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "志穂美", "answers": [ "しほみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "剛田", "answers": [ "ごうだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "上条", "answers": [ "かみじょう", "じょうじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 45%, 34%" },
	{ "question": "池水", "answers": [ "いけみず" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "井内", "answers": [ "いうち", "いない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "青砥", "answers": [ "あおと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 29%" },
	{ "question": "慕容", "answers": [ "ぼよう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "友清", "answers": [ "ともきよ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "新保", "answers": [ "しんぼ", "しんぽ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "槐", "answers": [ "さいかち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久留島", "answers": [ "くるしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "国木田", "answers": [ "くにきだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "数原", "answers": [ "かずはら", "すはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "井野", "answers": [ "いの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "浅茅", "answers": [ "あさぢ", "あさじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%, 22%" },
	{ "question": "上里", "answers": [ "うえさと", "あがり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "松沼", "answers": [ "まつぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "戸次", "answers": [ "とつぎ", "べっき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 75%, 25%" },
	{ "question": "東城", "answers": [ "とうじょう", "とうぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "多部", "answers": [ "たべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "杉下", "answers": [ "すぎした" ], "comment": "Frequency: 95%" },
	{ "question": "習", "answers": [ "しゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "小崎", "answers": [ "こざき", "おざき", "こさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 73%, 25%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "久原", "answers": [ "くはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "平吉", "answers": [ "ひらよし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%" },
	{ "question": "春江", "answers": [ "はるえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "代永", "answers": [ "よなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竹口", "answers": [ "たけぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "清武", "answers": [ "きよたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%" },
	{ "question": "清河", "answers": [ "きよかわ", "せいか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "伊良部", "answers": [ "いらぶ", "いらべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "石村", "answers": [ "いしむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "芳野", "answers": [ "よしの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%" },
	{ "question": "藤城", "answers": [ "ふじしろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "羽仁", "answers": [ "はに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "二谷", "answers": [ "にたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "頭山", "answers": [ "とうやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小森田", "answers": [ "こもりた", "こもりだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 81%, 19%" },
	{ "question": "来宮", "answers": [ "きのみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 76%" },
	{ "question": "大八木", "answers": [ "おおやぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大鶴", "answers": [ "おおつる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "井深", "answers": [ "いぶか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朔", "answers": [ "さく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "八木沼", "answers": [ "やぎぬま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "平間", "answers": [ "ひらま", "へいま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "東久邇宮", "answers": [ "ひがしくにのみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "永澤", "answers": [ "ながさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "高沢", "answers": [ "たかざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "三隅", "answers": [ "みすみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "羽原", "answers": [ "はばら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "花岡", "answers": [ "はなおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "滝本", "answers": [ "たきもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "相米", "answers": [ "そうまい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "陶山", "answers": [ "すやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "下平", "answers": [ "しもひら", "しもだいら", "しもたいら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 63%, 23%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "島木", "answers": [ "しまき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "九里", "answers": [ "くり", "くのり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 48%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "北別府", "answers": [ "きたべっぷ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "烏丸", "answers": [ "からすま", "からすまる" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "春日野", "answers": [ "かすがの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "樫山", "answers": [ "かしやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "小高", "answers": [ "おだか", "こだか", "こたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 6%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "浦辺", "answers": [ "うらべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "植竹", "answers": [ "うえたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "池山", "answers": [ "いけやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "赤沢", "answers": [ "あかざわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "愛野", "answers": [ "あいの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%" },
	{ "question": "吉高", "answers": [ "よしたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真崎", "answers": [ "まさき", "さなざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "堀之内", "answers": [ "ほりのうち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%" },
	{ "question": "竹岡", "answers": [ "たけおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "島野", "answers": [ "しまの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "堺屋", "answers": [ "さかいや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "五社", "answers": [ "ごしゃ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "琴光喜", "answers": [ "ことみつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "倉沢", "answers": [ "くらさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "黄川田", "answers": [ "きかわだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "石谷", "answers": [ "いしがや", "いしたに", "いしがい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 69%, 19%, 5%" },
	{ "question": "真中", "answers": [ "まなか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "本城", "answers": [ "ほんじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "穂口", "answers": [ "ほぐち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "藤浦", "answers": [ "ふじうら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "周防", "answers": [ "すほう", "すお", "すおう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 36%, 33%, 31%" },
	{ "question": "郷", "answers": [ "ごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "越中", "answers": [ "こしなか", "えっちゅう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "鴻池", "answers": [ "こうのいけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "柄谷", "answers": [ "からたに" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "阿倍", "answers": [ "あべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "流", "answers": [ "ながれ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%" },
	{ "question": "重長", "answers": [ "しげなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "山辺", "answers": [ "やまべ", "やまのべ", "やまへ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%, 4%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "船場", "answers": [ "せんば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "横谷", "answers": [ "よこたに", "よこや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "箭内", "answers": [ "やない" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "北勝海", "answers": [ "ほくとうみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "疋田", "answers": [ "ひきた", "ひきだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 54%, 39%" },
	{ "question": "立松", "answers": [ "たてまつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "井村", "answers": [ "いむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "五井", "answers": [ "ごい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "尹", "answers": [ "ユン", "いん", "ゆん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 37%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "弓削", "answers": [ "ゆげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "室", "answers": [ "むろ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "満島", "answers": [ "みつしま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真地", "answers": [ "まち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "古尾谷", "answers": [ "ふるおや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "西堀", "answers": [ "にしぼり", "にしほり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "中舘", "answers": [ "なかだて" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "豊永", "answers": [ "とよなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "武川", "answers": [ "たけかわ", "むかわ", "たけがわ", "むがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%, 25%, 9%, 7%" },
	{ "question": "清野", "answers": [ "せいの", "きよの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 40%" },
	{ "question": "新房", "answers": [ "しんぼう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "志垣", "answers": [ "しがき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "江頭", "answers": [ "えがしら", "えとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "伊佐山", "answers": [ "いさやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "中町", "answers": [ "なかまち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%" },
	{ "question": "三ツ木", "answers": [ "みつぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "中邑", "answers": [ "なかむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "時東", "answers": [ "ときとう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "田渕", "answers": [ "たぶち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佐高", "answers": [ "さたか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "車田", "answers": [ "くるまだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "柏戸", "answers": [ "かしわど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "亜蘭", "answers": [ "あらん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 80%" },
	{ "question": "邯鄲", "answers": [ "かんたん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "山脇", "answers": [ "やまわき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "福元", "answers": [ "ふくもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "半場", "answers": [ "はんば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "寺井", "answers": [ "てらい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 78%" },
	{ "question": "都筑", "answers": [ "つづき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%" },
	{ "question": "金剛", "answers": [ "こんごう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 46%" },
	{ "question": "古城", "answers": [ "こしろ", "ふるき", "こじょう", "ふるじょう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 44%, 31%, 19%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "神取", "answers": [ "かんどり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "佐和", "answers": [ "さわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 34%" },
	{ "question": "谷戸", "answers": [ "たにど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 40%" },
	{ "question": "猪谷", "answers": [ "いがや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 37%" },
	{ "question": "菱川", "answers": [ "ひしかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "額賀", "answers": [ "ぬかが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "十川", "answers": [ "そご", "そがわ", "とがわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 59%, 19%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "重村", "answers": [ "しげむら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%" },
	{ "question": "巨勢", "answers": [ "こせ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "桐山", "answers": [ "きりやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "尾田", "answers": [ "おだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "赤堀", "answers": [ "あかほり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 93%" },
	{ "question": "山際", "answers": [ "やまぎわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "眞木", "answers": [ "まき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%" },
	{ "question": "畑山", "answers": [ "はたけやま", "はたやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 66%, 34%" },
	{ "question": "竹宮", "answers": [ "たけみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "貴ノ花", "answers": [ "たかのはな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "初代", "answers": [ "しょだい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "源田", "answers": [ "げんだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "粟屋", "answers": [ "あわや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%" },
	{ "question": "盛重", "answers": [ "もりしげ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 14%" },
	{ "question": "奈月", "answers": [ "なつき", "なづき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 21%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "和木", "answers": [ "わき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 3%" },
	{ "question": "満田", "answers": [ "みつた", "みつだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 52%, 48%" },
	{ "question": "松橋", "answers": [ "まつはし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%" },
	{ "question": "舞の海", "answers": [ "まいのうみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "朝永", "answers": [ "ともなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "冨岡", "answers": [ "とみおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "下屋", "answers": [ "したや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宇川", "answers": [ "うかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "市来", "answers": [ "いちき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%" },
	{ "question": "大輝", "answers": [ "だいき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%" },
	{ "question": "譚", "answers": [ "たん", "タン" ], "comment": "Frequency: 32%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "一枝", "answers": [ "いちえだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 30%" },
	{ "question": "開", "answers": [ "ひらき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "鳴沢", "answers": [ "なるさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 15%" },
	{ "question": "印南", "answers": [ "いんなみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "吉木", "answers": [ "よしき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梁川", "answers": [ "やながわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%" },
	{ "question": "奈良原", "answers": [ "ならはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仲木", "answers": [ "なかぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "関島", "answers": [ "せきじま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "白坂", "answers": [ "しらさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "里崎", "answers": [ "さとざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "大鹿", "answers": [ "おおしか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 23%" },
	{ "question": "宮永", "answers": [ "みやなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "松森", "answers": [ "まつもり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 65%" },
	{ "question": "真柴", "answers": [ "ましば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "二本柳", "answers": [ "にほんやなぎ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蠣崎", "answers": [ "かきざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "押尾", "answers": [ "おしお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "天宮", "answers": [ "あまみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蔵前", "answers": [ "くらまえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 8%" },
	{ "question": "稲毛", "answers": [ "いなげ", "いなけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 26%, 9%" },
	{ "question": "耶律", "answers": [ "やりつ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "宮路", "answers": [ "みやじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "光田", "answers": [ "みつだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "美樹本", "answers": [ "みきもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "星崎", "answers": [ "ほしざき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梶本", "answers": [ "かじもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "小枝", "answers": [ "こえだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "淀", "answers": [ "よど" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "和辻", "answers": [ "わつじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山花", "answers": [ "やまはな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "山野辺", "answers": [ "やまのべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "保岡", "answers": [ "やすおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "谷澤", "answers": [ "やざわ", "たにざわ", "たにさわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%, 5%, 4%" },
	{ "question": "把瑠都", "answers": [ "ばると" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "春山", "answers": [ "はるやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 96%" },
	{ "question": "寺川", "answers": [ "てらかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "木俣", "answers": [ "きまた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "霍", "answers": [ "かく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "池乃", "answers": [ "いけの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "浅岡", "answers": [ "あさおか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真己", "answers": [ "まき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 4%" },
	{ "question": "丹", "answers": [ "たん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 25%" },
	{ "question": "武久", "answers": [ "たけひさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "雪見", "answers": [ "ゆきみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "山尾", "answers": [ "やまお" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "明神", "answers": [ "みょうじん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%" },
	{ "question": "美木", "answers": [ "みき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "野添", "answers": [ "のぞえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "二ノ宮", "answers": [ "にのみや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "長江", "answers": [ "ながえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%" },
	{ "question": "中園", "answers": [ "なかぞの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "新崎", "answers": [ "しんざき", "あらさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 79%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "小比類巻", "answers": [ "こひるいまき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "木本", "answers": [ "きもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 98%" },
	{ "question": "苅谷", "answers": [ "かりや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "梶田", "answers": [ "かじた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 92%" },
	{ "question": "風祭", "answers": [ "かざまつり" ], "comment": "Frequency: 82%" },
	{ "question": "海音寺", "answers": [ "かいおんじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "犬飼", "answers": [ "いぬかい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 89%" },
	{ "question": "兼平", "answers": [ "かねひら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 9%" },
	{ "question": "且元", "answers": [ "かつもと" ], "comment": "Frequency: 7%" },
	{ "question": "福住", "answers": [ "ふくずみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "山咲", "answers": [ "やまざき", "やまさき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 97%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "友永", "answers": [ "ともなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "平良", "answers": [ "たいら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蘇", "answers": [ "そ", "スー" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%, 12%" },
	{ "question": "澤野", "answers": [ "さわの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "窪塚", "answers": [ "くぼづか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "上野山", "answers": [ "うえのやま", "かみのやま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 94%, 6%" },
	{ "question": "岩渕", "answers": [ "いわぶち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "五輪", "answers": [ "いつわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "池脇", "answers": [ "いけわき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "弾", "answers": [ "だん" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "重徳", "answers": [ "しげとく" ], "comment": "Frequency: 6%" },
	{ "question": "当麻", "answers": [ "とうま" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "粟生", "answers": [ "あおう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 35%" },
	{ "question": "東出", "answers": [ "ひがしで" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "羽月", "answers": [ "はづき", "はつき" ], "comment": "Frequency: 85%, 8%" },
	{ "question": "中込", "answers": [ "なかごみ", "なかごめ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 49%, 28%" },
	{ "question": "関屋", "answers": [ "せきや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 57%" },
	{ "question": "杉井", "answers": [ "すぎい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "真堂", "answers": [ "しんどう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "是枝", "answers": [ "これえだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "古葉", "answers": [ "こば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "栗栖", "answers": [ "くりす", "くるす" ], "comment": "Frequency: 74%, 26%" },
	{ "question": "上", "answers": [ "かみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 41%" },
	{ "question": "伊地知", "answers": [ "いぢち", "いじち" ], "comment": "Frequency: 64%, 36%" },
	{ "question": "赤嶺", "answers": [ "あかみね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "初美", "answers": [ "はつみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 32%" },
	{ "question": "国貞", "answers": [ "くにさだ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 18%" },
	{ "question": "宗方", "answers": [ "むなかた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%" },
	{ "question": "不知火", "answers": [ "しらぬい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "阿井", "answers": [ "あい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "竜司", "answers": [ "りゅうじ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 5%" },
	{ "question": "涼花", "answers": [ "すずはな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 10%" },
	{ "question": "彩音", "answers": [ "あやね" ], "comment": "Frequency: 20%" },
	{ "question": "豊野", "answers": [ "とよの" ], "comment": "Frequency: 2%" },
	{ "question": "正名", "answers": [ "まさな" ], "comment": "Frequency: 70%" },
	{ "question": "花房", "answers": [ "はなぶさ", "はなふさ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 83%, 17%" },
	{ "question": "長谷見", "answers": [ "はせみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "二瓶", "answers": [ "にへい" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "堂上", "answers": [ "どのうえ", "どううえ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 86%, 14%" },
	{ "question": "姿", "answers": [ "すがた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "芝田", "answers": [ "しばた" ], "comment": "Frequency: 91%" },
	{ "question": "色部", "answers": [ "いろべ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "網干", "answers": [ "あぼし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 12%" },
	{ "question": "米川", "answers": [ "よねかわ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 88%" },
	{ "question": "柳下", "answers": [ "やなぎした", "やぎした" ], "comment": "Frequency: 90%, 10%" },
	{ "question": "南風", "answers": [ "みなかぜ", "はえ", "なんぷう" ], "comment": "Frequency: 60%, 3%, 2%" },
	{ "question": "帆足", "answers": [ "ほあし" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "百武", "answers": [ "ひゃくたけ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "東原", "answers": [ "ひがしはら", "とうばら", "とうはら" ], "comment": "Frequency: 77%, 15%, 3%" },
	{ "question": "道上", "answers": [ "どうじょう", "みちがみ" ], "comment": "Frequency: 67%, 21%" },
	{ "question": "堤下", "answers": [ "つつみした" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "蔦谷", "answers": [ "つたや" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "嗣永", "answers": [ "つぐなが" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "仙波", "answers": [ "せんば" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "久坂", "answers": [ "くさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 100%" },
	{ "question": "神坂", "answers": [ "かんざか", "こうさか", "かみさか" ], "comment": "Frequency: 62%, 34%, 3%" }
]
}
